I'm sorry you weren't meant to hear that.
But this is what you were meant to hear.
Freshly printed coke.
It's Friday!
And today is a special Friday special because it's Friday.
That's why it's a Friday special.
That's really nothing else to it.
I was just happy about the fact it being Friday, so that's why it's called Friday special.
No, sensei Pete!
Why would you put it on max?
I mean, yeah, fair enough.
I'm sorry.
What snacks did you get?
I got some, uh, what are they called?
Skillpiller.
What's the word for that in English?
Tortoises?
Chocolate tortoises.
I think it's a Danish thing.
But I ate a couple of those right before this.
So I'm pretty much going to be on a sugar high for the foreseeable future.
Oh yeah.
Friday special, it's like saying the same word twice.
That's so true.
Hey, Tyler!
Heyo!
Found your channel through your Minecraft playthrough.
I'm about halfway through the vods.
They're perfect for when I'm working.
Cheers from another PhD student from Canada.
Hey man!
Cheers!
I hope you're doing well.
Thanks for checking it out.
How's everybody doing, huh?
Special fight day.
I can't type properly on mobile?
How dare you watch this on mobile?
Actually, I'm just kidding, of course, but isn't it very difficult to watch Terraria
on mobile?
I feel like everything is so small in this game, it would be almost impossible to tell
what's going on.
Unless I zoom in all the way, right?
Hello, Oliver Person.
What's up, vTour person?
From one person to another person, how are you doing?
Yeah, there's no chat, so here's what I was thinking.
The chat over here now.
Because people said to me in the first stream, and I kind of forgot about it, that it was
covering some of the text on the left.
So hopefully this placement is okay.
I don't think there's anything in the game so far that has been in that position.
We should be fine, is what I'm saying.
Is it better?
I think it's better.
Also, I was looking through the controls, trying to optimize my keybinds here because
I had healing on H, and the zooms were on plus and minus.
I tried to bind it to the mouse wheel, didn't work.
So instead I went for the F keys, F1 and F2.
Let's see how this all works.
I need to get used to this.
But it felt a little awkward before, so I tried adjusting it, is what I'm saying.
And then I also found this.
Something called Autopause.
I'm not quite sure what it does, but I'll try to put it on and see what happens.
Maybe I'll turn it off.
It depends what it actually does.
It covers some inventory.
Oh, it does.
I can move it a bit to the left.
Key overlap?
Oh, no.
Do I have that?
When do I have key overlap?
Oh, yeah.
Right.
I do.
Let's do this.
A 5.
Camera mode can be...
I don't know what that is, but that's better.
I think that was it, right?
Yeah, thanks.
Good spot.
Thanks.
Okay.
I think I'm just going to jump right in, guys.
I'm excited to keep playing this game.
I feel like I haven't really gotten that far yet.
Although it also feels like I have gotten far.
It's a bit of a mixed bag.
I feel like I'm missing some very basic things when it comes to crafting.
I spent a lot of time on that last stream,
but I think I'm going to try to explore a bit more this time.
But also do crafting, of course.
I want to create my house and all that.
So, yeah.
I will close down chat here,
and I will see you guys on the other side.
Good luck, have fun.
Wait, didn't I have 200?
Mana?
I seem to remember these being the same.
Maybe not, I don't know.
Yeah, play.
Alright.
Okay then, let me quickly try my keybinds here.
Oh, that's way more comfortable.
Not as comfortable as using the scroll wheel,
but you know, it is what it is.
Why am I here again?
Didn't I lock out at the house?
I'm not sure.
What's up, people? I'm back.
Hanno, Dylan.
They're talking about fists and bunnies.
Hmm.
And we have Haley and Catalan.
She was a newcomer,
Mortal and Seymour.
Who's Seymour?
Sword beats paper.
Get one today.
Aha, right.
Yeah.
So, I was building, I believe.
Oh yeah, I also rebounded my inventory to Tab,
because pressing...
Wait, wait.
Okay, we're fine.
Pressing Escape every time was very uncomfortable.
So Tab is much more efficient for me.
And something else was on Tab before,
something regarding the minimap, but I think it's okay.
I have the map on M.
And then I can...
Oh, but wait, that was also the...
This one.
The style of map, okay.
Everything seems to be in order.
Dylan is talking to Hanno again.
And Hanno is mad!
He's saying fishing.
Go fishing for spiders.
It'll be great.
Yeah, it'll be hot.
And we can do some mining, too.
What do you think?
Yeah, we can relax on the desert?
But we need water, then.
It's very hot there, and there's fish, you know?
Yeah, and old people everywhere, trust me.
Okay, I think they're looping it.
I don't know.
Alright, let's see here.
What do I have?
I have some money on me.
I have flaming arrows.
Water buckets.
So I'm gonna prepare my inventory for adventure now.
I am gonna go straight on an adventure.
But...
Hold on.
The gun.
So I figured out last time that I could potentially buy ammo
from someone who came here if I had a gun.
And I have a gun.
Was it more tall I could buy from?
It was someone regarding ammo, dynamite, my own special cure.
No, you were just explosives.
What do you actually sell? Let me just quickly see.
Piggy bank.
Can be used to store your items?
Stored items can only be accessed by you.
Sure.
I mean, that's cute, I guess.
Pinwheel?
Rope.
I'm actually curious about this.
Hold on. Stored items can only be accessed by you?
Is that the same...
craft?
Wait a minute.
I need to see something real quick.
Do we have a box?
Chest.
Stored items can only be accessed by you.
Wait, what does that mean?
Does that mean NPCs can access my items in these?
Or it's got to be like a multiplayer thing.
Give me this.
I mean, it's obviously...
Oh, we also have this one. Yeah, cellus harpoon.
That one is crazy good.
So I have three weapons right now,
but I don't have any ammo for the undertaker.
Wait, no.
Tap.
Wait, how do I...
What's happening?
Oh, wait.
Oh, the game is paused now.
It just occurred to me.
So I can...
This is not good, then, because I can't actually...
I can't do anything.
That's that... No, I don't like that.
We're gonna have to revert that immediately.
Maybe I'll experiment with it later on,
but right now that's pretty annoying.
The way that works.
Okay.
Oh yeah, much better.
Let's put this on a...
I can put it here, I guess.
I can also put it...
No, I need to put it up here.
Piggy bank.
Shit, that's not what I wanted to do.
The loot all.
Actually, it just occurred to me.
Can I... Can I put this anywhere?
Oh right, it's gonna default over here, of course.
Holy shit.
I feel stupid right now.
I could have just placed my items in a chest,
and then I wouldn't lose it when I die.
But now that I have a piggy bank,
it's more fitting, I guess.
I just don't like that it's pink.
Well, I guess pigs are pink.
I don't know why I just said that.
Oh my god.
Yup, pigs are pink.
Well, not pink, but you know.
You know what I mean.
Where's our Michelin... This is our Michelinius.
Game's a bit too loud for me, let me just adjust that.
Let's put this in here, and trash can.
I'm gonna put that somewhere.
Let's put it there.
Oh, we can put trash items in here.
That would be amazing.
Put in...
Lens.
Everything that's random.
I'm gonna bring this for my adventures.
Right, I also have... Man, I have a lot of...
Different weapons.
The wall goes in construction.
There it is.
Also that, and...
I'm gonna bring this.
Because this is good for the caves.
Sticky bomb.
Bognet is good to have.
Worm.
Organics.
Ladybug.
And then all the ores and doors.
Put it in here.
No, wait, actually, I do want the dirt.
The dirt is actually super useful when exploring.
This is my food.
I need this.
Man, I want to figure out a way to create some actual good food
so I can heal myself properly
instead of relying on finding potions.
That's my biggest issue.
I only have two of them right now.
And I need to survive in these dungeons and shit.
You know, I can't play block.
Put them in here.
I can't just rely on finding it.
What just happened there?
Something just popped down there.
Was it a balloon?
Wood goes in here.
Lead bar? Put it in...
Wait. No, no, no.
Did I just fuck this up?
I'm terrible at this.
Construction.
In you go. There we go.
Then ores and doors. In you go.
And look at this inventory. It's beautiful.
It is clean.
And I think I'm going to experiment with the loadouts as well.
Because I'm finding a lot of different items.
And maybe I want to change it quickly.
At some point.
And by that I can just go like this.
And everything changes immediately.
So that's actually pretty cool.
Now the gun...
Has no ammo.
But I'm going to bring it anyway in case I find more ammo.
Maybe, I mean, I found ammo out there once, right?
But for now I guess I can replace it here.
Because it doesn't have any ammo.
And the fishing rod, I'll also leave at home.
Now wait potions.
Oh yeah, definitely. Bring these.
And...
Gramps invisibility.
Yeah, you know what? Bring these as well.
Not that.
I have 49 of these. Holy shit.
Okay.
Michelinius.
I need a weapons and utility chest here.
Let's make it this one over here.
Rename.
And let's call this...
Weapon...
Weapons...
That's a good start.
You know what? Let's put this one in here.
I mean, it's not really a weapon, but you know what I mean.
The axe I'll bring.
Maybe I'll need it.
And the rest seems okay, doesn't it?
Okay. Oh, actually, there is one thing.
Where is it?
Nice. I have the grappling hook. Look at this.
This is so sick.
I can't wait to try this, like for real.
Okay, are we ready?
Okay, you know what?
These stairs are actually kind of annoying.
Because every time you walk this way, it automatically walks up.
And I have to sort of go like that.
I need to find a solution to that.
So the question is...
Where do we go?
Of course, we're going east.
And I have my weapons.
I'm so ready, dude.
What's that?
It's a cardinal.
What's that? Is that water?
Looks like water.
Dirty water.
We're so back.
So I need to find potions here.
Potion seller.
I require your strongest potions.
Should I be catching these?
Crimson rod. Should I be... hold on.
How about I equip this stuff?
I could equip this as an
immediately emergency recall.
Nah.
That's easy enough to click like that. Click there and click there.
That's not that bad.
Also, a setting I was confused about
was
autoselect.
I have no idea.
Like, it autoselects a torch
and then it has like a pickaxe.
Okay.
So it autoselects the tool for the job.
But what about the torch though?
That's what I don't understand here.
Oh no. Already taking damage.
This is not a good sign.
Let's eat the mushroom.
At least we have a good amount of mushrooms here.
So, a question I have.
This restores 15 life, but I
I swear to you, look, 172.
That's gonna go to 200.
Watch.
Oh, fuck.
Didn't mean to do that.
Look, it keeps going.
I don't get that.
It's like the food is way more potent
than it actually says.
That's so confusing.
Oh no, we're in scary country again.
Wait!
Bro! We never retrieved our gold!
I'm going for that.
That...
Also, we need to summon...
No, I didn't bring Abigail.
That's such a mistake.
Ah, well, fuck.
It's okay.
We don't need Abigail.
Okay.
Let's just calm down here.
Okay, that was sort of smooth.
But only sort of.
Uh...
What is this here?
Can I destroy that?
The fuck?
It's clearly different
than this red stuff right here.
I take damage from it, I think.
I was standing here once and I took damage.
Let's see.
Actually, maybe not.
Crimestone block.
Wait.
Wasn't Crimstone the thing I needed?
There was a block that
I could make a pickaxe
out of, like, a very good one.
I forgot what it was.
Ah, fuck this guy. I'm just going to keep moving.
I believe I went this way
and then... oh, I can actually look at the map.
That's where I went last time
and that's where my gold is.
I will retrieve that.
Okay, here's the mission.
I will retrieve the gold and immediately teleport home.
Because I believe that was a lot of gold.
So let's play this ultra safe.
Let's not be dummies.
Gosh, come here.
There we go.
And let's play it ultra safe. By the way,
today we're not going to die. It's going to be a deathless dream.
What's that?
There's something right there. You see that?
Oh, lead.
It was sort of embedded in the back somehow.
That was interesting.
Okay, so I went down here.
Oh, here we go.
I am also curious,
what the fuck happened
last time I was here?
That was like a...
a boss.
Extracted by creeper?
It's always the creepers, isn't it?
Right, keep going down.
What is this right here again?
Ah, shit.
Is this just background?
Okay, whatever.
I'm playing this ultra safe, and we also have to be on the lookout for
falling rocks.
That killed me a lot last time.
Why did it suddenly get so dark?
What did I just do?
The double jump is a game changer.
Look at that.
Here we go.
Oh, there's actually a detonator.
I'm going to take that with me.
So, is this really just a way to...
Hold on.
Do I not need to have my pickaxe equipped at all for this?
Is that like the trick here?
I don't even need to have it in my bar.
That's what that does.
Holy shit.
I see the use now.
I get it.
That's a piranha.
Then I went down.
Who the fuck is that?
A skeleton.
Let me actually...
Oh, see, now I'm instinctively clicking on my pickaxe icon.
But I have to get used to the fact that I just go shift.
What? No!
Why does it select the torch?
I don't understand that.
Okay, that's fine.
A torch is needed there anyway.
But I guess that also means I don't have my...
need to have my torch...
God, that's actually annoying.
Okay, maybe I do want my thing here.
That's actually fucking annoying.
Stop blazing torches!
God damn.
Oh, I did not see this last time.
Maybe there's a setting to turn off the auto torch functionality there.
Okay, there.
And then...
Mouse.
Ooh, I kind of want to catch that.
That's an enemy.
Then we go down.
That is a salamander.
Also, I need to remember, what is my healing key mine?
I need to see this.
Uh...
Q...
I put it on Q, okay.
Perfect.
Dummy.
You're so dumb.
What's that?
Emeralds.
Also, there was this weapon here,
that I want to do some more stuff with.
Oh.
Let me just take it really...
Ooh, that up there looks...
pretty bad, doesn't it?
That ain't good.
I wonder what this material is right here.
What's that?
Uh-oh, someone's coming.
Switch to this.
Actually a decent weapon.
There's such a big difference
in the way these weapons are.
Kind of neat.
What's that?
Teal mushroom.
Torch.
Oh, here's the thing.
Let me use platform here.
And...
Wait.
Oh, that was sick!
You can totally do some shenanigans like that.
Wait.
Wait, we've got something in here?
That, I believe, is amethyst?
No, sapphire.
Lovely.
I'll take anything here.
Put a torch.
And then we go like this.
Look at that, look at those skills, dude.
What's up, guys?
How you doing?
Good.
I love the sound effect of this harpoon.
These guys have a lot of HP.
Maybe it's not that great, actually.
Oh, God!
Fuck, that scared me.
Teal. I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready!
Come on, bring it on.
Mother hacker.
That's right.
Are they stuck on that little piece there?
Oh, God.
Please don't die now, please don't die now!
I need to chill here.
Come on.
Scary.
Okay, let's chillax for a moment.
Okay, I need to wait a bit.
Or I can heal again.
Where's my money?
Uh-oh, what's that? Antlion Swarmer.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Dude, I just had an idea.
What if I just put a door?
Ho!
I gotta eat this.
I can't use my last healing potion.
We need to be very conservative here.
Hold on, can I?
Shit, okay.
Come on.
Okay, that worked pretty well.
Don't die!
Also, when they're close, you can spam it really quick.
Because it resets whenever it hits an enemy.
So close range, this thing is amazing.
Look at that!
That's great!
Oh, God. We've got incoming.
Let's stay up here.
Oh!
There we go.
Okay, we're almost full health.
See, how will we full health from a mushroom?
There's something I'm not...
Oh, I should put down a campfire, dude.
Holy shit!
That's...
A banana split!
That's my favorite dessert!
Medium improvements to all stats.
Make like a banana and split!
Split!
Yes!
Also, can I stack this stuff?
Let's see here.
So I have this one plenty satisfied.
Wait, we got incoming.
Oh, look at the DPS!
When you're close,
that shit hits like a truck.
That's a waste of a thingy.
Is that cactus gonna damage me?
Yeah, I knew it.
I knew it.
Take care of this dude here.
Man, that's great.
That does so much damage.
Uh, give me this.
Now, where did I go?
Where did I die? Here!
Where's my money?
I'm playing so safe right now,
because I don't want to die.
Give me this.
Well, you know what?
Hey, my dude!
Oh, that was terrible.
Look at this.
No!
Oh, we've got lava here.
Also, what is inside these?
What?
It started rolling?
Okay, I don't like that.
I don't like this either.
Actually, I love that.
I love that it's burning.
I'm just gonna take a sip here and watch this guy suffer.
See this thing up here?
I'm scared of now, so I'm actually gonna do
the logical and smart thing.
Which is...
Now it's not gonna fall on me anymore.
I'm gonna do the same thing here.
Wow, that does a lot of damage!
I think it may be based on the height
from which it falls.
Ooh, that's enemies.
Antlion?
Swarmers?
For now, I'm just gonna...
If you guys don't mind, I'm just gonna
block you in there.
Look at them dying down there.
Fuck!
That's the problem with the sticky bomb.
It's a little bit more difficult to...
You know.
If I drop down there, I'm surely gonna die.
So, let's be smart about this.
Haha!
Ooh, yeah. Those fall.
Why can't... Oh, I'm standing on something.
Okay, okay. And then...
Just block that shit off.
Let's be ultra safe here.
Now, where did I...
Did I die down here? Hold on.
I see some money there.
Copper coin?
I'm not sure. It's a little bit hard to tell.
I'm gonna make my way in there from over here.
Dude, I love being in the caves.
The caves make me happy.
Such a nice sense of adventure.
I also like this music here.
Is this my money?
What is that sound going?
Also, this is gonna spawn one of these.
Oh look! They can trigger each other.
No, I have not recovered my money at all.
Not even close.
What? There we go.
What's that? Wooden arrow?
Yes! That's what I needed.
What's this?
Honestly, I think my money may be gone.
I think the money is gone.
Oh shit. Oh god!
I'm fine. These guys don't do any damage at all.
It's just the effect of getting hit.
The screen shakes.
The screen shakes on your character.
It makes me scared.
Wait, what is this thing over here?
That doesn't look cavey.
That looks man-made.
Oh my god, I can't hit shit from here.
Oh and now you're coming!
Motherfucker!
Eat this.
Uh oh!
Just bring it on.
Bring it on, sir.
Come on.
No you want to...
Here it is.
What?
Wait, are these minecarts?
God, these things are so...
Can I walk on this?
I can't.
There we go.
Oh, we dropped.
Nice.
Oh, there's a jar.
I need that.
Cool.
Why are there...
These look like mine tracks to me.
Uh...
Hold on, I have an idea.
I should use this some more.
It's really nice.
You just mine this while you get killed.
Cool.
That feels great, doesn't it?
There's a statue there of something.
Uh oh.
We've got incoming.
Actually, we don't.
Wait a minute.
I just had a...
Yep, I had a minecart symbol look.
Oh!
What?
I didn't even realize I had a minecart.
Oh God, I feel like this is a bad idea.
What if I'm...
Okay, just go.
Just...
Ooh, what's this now?
We're in Mushroom County.
Okay.
I can jump with the thing.
That's amazing.
I just want to get out, please.
How do I...
Am I being really dumb?
Wait.
Uh...
What the...
Okay, that worked.
Also, I kind of forgot I had this!
Oh my God!
I need...
I need to remember that.
My goodness, like...
Look at this!
It's so useful!
It's actually absurdly useful.
Oh my God, you can just...
You can go anywhere and do anything.
Wow.
And I can just stand here and plink away.
If I want to.
Oh, I knew it!
No, I saw the button.
I was like, what does this do?
And the moment I
fucking stepped on it,
I thought it's probably a trap.
Oh, I'm so dumb.
Aw, man. First death doesn't count, remember?
Dylan, uh...
Do you have a thing for, uh, Catlin here?
He was talking about her. I saw that.
I saw that, Dylan.
Um...
Also, should I maybe you'd be using my bow a bit more?
It is a pretty sick bow.
It's a tungsten bow.
And I have fire arrows, so, you know...
Oh...
I think I just realized.
This is what those are.
It's the visual of your
extra items you have equipped.
This makes more sense now.
Also, what are these?
I'm kind of water plant.
A plant underwater.
Hey.
You stupid vulture.
Give me that money.
Now, I may actually have lost my money somewhere else
down in that cave.
It's possible, but I just seem to remember
it was down there with, uh...
with those...
monsters there.
The desert monsters.
Back now we go...
Also, notice how...
this red stuff is spreading to here.
It's like making my dirt into that material.
Crimestone.
Oh, god.
Okay, then we go here.
Hold on, can I use my hammer on this?
What? How did I just take damage?
I don't understand what just happened.
Aha!
Wait a second now.
Whoops.
Come on.
What...
is going on?
It's not doing damage to me when I'm just standing here.
But if I hit it with the hammer,
then I take damage from it.
Oh, I'm taking this...
I'm taking this door.
Wooden arrow. Nice.
Like, look at my HP. It's...
it's regenerating still.
Okay, nice.
Uh, yep. Keep going down.
I feel like my torches are disappearing.
Oh, maybe not.
Okay, go here.
Uh, should be safe down here.
I have cleared this path extensively
and made it safe.
Nice.
Is that a thing that can fall?
No.
Nice.
I keep forgetting I have this. God damn it.
Can I also... Okay, here's a quick test.
What if I go like this?
Huh.
That's not bad.
I'm liking that.
Uh, then I go across here.
Oh, be careful of the thingy.
Oh man, it's so useful.
I definitely need to get used to just
using it and have it be second nature.
It's an insane item.
And it demands my respect.
That's what I think.
Did I take all this shit?
It's so odd.
What is this piss vessel?
Okay, so look, look.
You see that? That's a god damn stone.
Wait, really? I can't...
Wait.
Aw, come on.
No way.
What if I release it?
Wait, what if I
go like that and I shoot?
How do I
trip this trap?
Huh.
That works.
Oh my god.
More sapphire.
Bro, this hook...
I can just go like this?
I don't even need to use my
feet. I can just go. Look at this.
That's crazy.
Oh, we've got loot up here.
I actually got to go get that.
We also got a... we also have a thing here.
Oh my god.
You're not getting away.
There we go.
That was... that was personal.
This hook is a little awkward to use.
I need to really get used to this.
Oh, there's a thing in the way. I see.
There we go. Nice.
And what is that?
Tin, I believe.
Yeah, let's just take it.
I mean, there's no reason not to, right?
If I see it, grab it.
I learned that lesson in Minecraft.
Then we go down into the right.
Full health, perfect.
I wonder if this weapon does more damage to the closer they are.
I mean, not just from the attack speed, but...
Bring it on.
Come on. I know you want to.
Maybe I should just go grab my...
money immediately.
Oh man.
So annoying.
Are you not dead yet? There we go.
That was kind of sick actually.
I got it.
It was not a lot of gold, but you know...
It's something.
It's definitely something.
So, here's the question. I don't even have a minecart on me.
But yet, I can just do this.
That's confusing me because I was able to craft a minecart earlier.
I think...
Oh. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Get away from me. Don't damage me.
Vicious mushroom? I should probably not eat that, right?
Oh, I can't even eat that.
Eat the last of this.
Oh wait, I can do this.
Oh, that's the sickest strategy.
Just hang on and then mine.
That's like a game changer.
Yo!
Here's my question.
What happens if I destroy the block I'm holding on to?
I fall down. That makes a lot of sense, I guess.
Oh my god. Get off of me.
Oh no, the mine thingy.
Please get away from me.
Oh, this weapon is so much better in close quarter.
I should use some potions.
Let's grant invisibility.
Let's try that.
Wow, I'm actually full-on invisible.
I can't even see myself.
I feel like that's not great.
Uh...
Oh, and then I appear when I do...
Oh, okay.
That is interesting.
Okay, we're super stealthy right now.
Hey, bastard!
Oh, he did.
Fuck this.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Yep. That's nice.
That's nice. Look at these fools.
I'm in a mine cart.
And I have good feelings about it.
And you're dead.
This is awesome.
Definitely want to make mine carts.
Oh!
Oh, I was trying to hit it with it.
Let's just clear all these traps.
Oh! Okay, we're fine.
Drive by shooting.
Yeah!
Hit it.
Oh, yeah!
My goodness.
How do I just exit the mine cart?
Oh, okay. I can right-click the icon.
That's actually pretty good to know.
Let's put down some lights.
I'm liking this cave.
This cave is awesome.
How is that rolling like that?
The acceleration here on the items
makes zero sense.
I have a scarab bomb.
A narrow explosion that will destroy most tiles.
Explosion aims away from your precision.
Let's try it.
Oh!
Yo!
Whoa! That's a crazy bomb!
Oh, god.
Heal.
Yo, that bomb...
is...
wild!
We have another one.
Sturdy fossil?
Wait, do I not have my...
Eat the lobster tail?
How much does he actually give me?
I have 20 defense.
I don't know whether or not that's good.
Uh, mine all this.
Doo-doo-doo.
Dude, I love exploring.
Very satisfying so far.
Oh! Whoa, whoa, whoa, what's happening?
Oh, man.
The damage effect really messes with me.
Desert torch and rope.
Ooh, listen to the sound of the lava.
That's scary.
Should I keep going down?
I don't know, man.
I'm kind of scared of going down.
I want to follow this mine track.
Oh! We've got an antlion.
Wait, that breaks easily.
Wait, is this all fossil?
Desert fossil?
Huh.
Let me grab some of that.
Okay, here we go.
It's such an interesting weapon, this one.
Because it really rewards precision,
but if you miss, you're open for...
trouble, you know?
Like, it's not good.
Oh, really? How's that not...
Thank you.
Bro! Bro!
Okay, okay.
Too slow.
Too slow, bro.
Oh, okay, you're kind of fast.
I can respect it. Come here.
It's really hard to deal with enemies
that just walk through tiles like that.
This is awkward as hell.
Wow.
That just revealed a torch.
I keep forgetting I have this damn hook!
See, that one is dangerous. Let's be careful here.
Okay, I think I understand how these work now.
They always accelerate in the direction
opposite from where they get hit.
I think.
Switch the weapon, please.
Here it comes.
Nice, I was ready for that one.
So, look at this.
If I go here now, and I hit this,
it's going right.
Beast stat... best statue!
Increases defense by five
when placed nearby.
Wait, really? So, if I do that,
can I just remove it again?
Yo, that's...
that's kind of...
crazy, isn't it?
I guess I'll just
have that ready.
Flaming arrow, nice, torches,
invisibility potion, tungsten,
suspicious looking eye.
Summons the eye of Qtulhu.
I mean...
Why would I... like a boss?
My question is why would I do that?
Uh...
But then my question is
why shouldn't I do that? Maybe the boss drops
some good shit.
Come here.
Fuckers.
This is so silly.
You know what I want in this game?
I want a machine gun.
I want something that goes...
I just shoot everything down with an AK.
That's what I want.
And another banana split!
I love it.
Okay.
Watch out for falling rocks.
Ooh, something's...
Oh! Look at this.
Look at this here.
Yep, that's how we do it.
I can kill those guys
while I chill here.
And we've got treasure!
I love it!
What did I just get? Gallius the traveling merchant
has arrived.
By the way...
By the way, I'm going to try
and remember to take a break this time
because I get absorbed by this game so much
that I forget to take a break.
And it's kind of important that I take a break.
And I will ask you about how the chat placement is.
Maybe it's blocking something still.
I don't know, but we'll see.
I'm going to try and remember to take a break.
Okay, this is scary.
No!
I think it's fine. Oh, we've got a guy.
Guy is gone.
Guy got disintegrated.
Guy had no chance.
Oh, what's that?
What is that?
I'm going there.
We've got a guy.
Come here, guy.
There we go.
Sturdy fossil.
Thank you very much.
Let me get rid of that.
Nice. I feel like I'm getting pretty good at this game.
Again!
I was quick this time.
Wait, what's that?
Man, I'm good. Give me that.
Wait.
Use the shift button.
I want to try and get used to this.
Maybe it's worth it, you know?
I want to push this guy away and then use this.
I think that sort of worked.
Oh, god. Oh, god.
Ah!
Wait, I just did something.
I went invisible somehow.
I think I clicked the wrong button.
That was not my intention.
I was just spamming my keyboard to heal just now
because I couldn't remember what my keyboard was.
Amber.
I feel like that's a new one.
I should be placing torches. So what is this?
What do we have here?
Crimson or...
That's the thing I need.
That is the thing I need.
Damn it.
Wait, archery?
Archery?
I have no clue, bro.
Get rid of that.
I really have a lot of shit in my inventory.
Let's delete some stuff.
Let's delete the door and...
No.
Let's also get rid of...
Let's see here.
Cobwebs.
The detonator.
Wait, what is this?
Used to make teal die.
Get rid of...
Okay, okay.
Man, I hate this sound.
There's enemies.
Let's go down.
This is scary, so let me...
Got more treasure.
Have I found any ammo at all?
Oh wait, I can't see. I don't have my gun.
I mean, I find...
Oh, look at this!
That's a treasure chamber!
Fuck yeah, dude!
Money? And what else?
Throw...
Another baste stack. Will that stack?
It will.
I have one of these already, but I'll take another one.
Dynamite?
I kind of want to try that, actually.
Healing potions!
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Too gold!
This is amazing.
Let's get rid of...
Active Stone...
What is Active Stone block?
The first thing I think of when I see this
is Redstone from Minecraft.
So maybe I'll keep it, actually.
If that's actually how that works.
Archery potion...
What can I get rid of?
There's... No, I want to keep that as well.
Let's get rid of the rope.
And let's keep the dynamite.
What's that?
Bone skeleton statue?
Nobody wants that.
Okay, we're fine.
I love this song right here.
This is a great song.
It hypes me up.
Why can't I pick up this healing potion?
I have room.
What am I missing?
Huh?
Maybe put this back?
Wait, what? Hold on, hold on.
Why can't I pick up this money?
Oh!
That's why!
I just realized...
Put...
something away.
Okay, actually eat this banana split.
Free up some inventory. Can we stack these then?
No.
So you can only have one of those at a time, it seems.
Get hit by that!
Aw!
Bastard.
Incoming!
Let me also grab all this.
Look at this. I'm just holding on with my grabble hook.
Here we go.
See ya.
Sucker.
Oh, one good thing I did, because look at this.
We've got items in there.
Dude, I love loot.
Ooh, that's scary.
What if that thing falls on me?
That's money.
Give me that, give me that.
Ooh! Okay, we're fine.
Get rid of this, and then we go like this.
Oh, no!
Red alert, red alert!
Oh, God.
Okay, we're actually okay.
I thought we took more damage there.
Everything is fine.
For some reason, this music reminds me of the mummy.
You know the movie, Brendan Fraser?
Reminds me of that vibe.
And I like it.
Because that movie slaps.
Get rid of all this cobweb.
There's a guy down there.
Golfer!
There's a golfer down here.
He's trying to golf this ant lion.
Look at that, he's practicing his swing.
Put this back.
Ooh, you're shooting things, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um...
Look at that, that's how we do it.
Are you okay, golfer?
Hold on, let me clear the area first.
Oh, he's gone.
I'm scared about this cactus right there.
Nice.
Golfer, why thank you?
I've been stuck in this sand pit for days!
Good thing you can get water out of a cactus.
Wait, what?
Actually?
Tell me about happiness.
I need a place to hang out my clubs.
Nothing better than having all this space to yourself.
Tell me something.
How am I supposed to golf in a place like the underground?
You know, that's a fair point.
I will, uh...
see to it.
Shop?
I can...
buy a worn golf club.
A well-rounded golf club, best for mid-range distances.
Golf balls will carry a good distance with...
decent vertical loft.
What the f...
Lawn mower?
What the fuck is this game?
Mow's pure and hallowed grass.
What is pure grass?
Mowed grass reduces enemy spawn chance?
You are shitting me.
Oh, we will be mowing lawns.
Golf whistle.
Returns your last hit golf ball to its previous position.
That's a 15 gold.
Uh, wait.
Are you guys just gonna stay down here?
Are you gonna make your way back to town?
Lion pines!
Don't go chasing water hazards.
Please stick to the fairways and greens that you're used to.
Okay, okay, well, sure.
What else do you say?
I'm not the type to scream and thrash around
just because my ball lands in the water.
I stay calm and collected
and focus on the next shot.
How are you saying all this down here?
There's a heart!
Oh, brother.
I am liking that.
Rid of all this.
Uh, hopefully you're just gonna head back at some point.
Oh, the skills.
Man, how far can I go?
220 now.
That's insanity.
Got more mine, uh, tracks here.
Oh, god.
Galeos has left!
I need to heal.
Nice. Uh, and then I need to...
I kind of want to do this.
I kind of want to summon the Eye of Cthulhu again.
I got my ass kicked to that thing.
Uh, Lyon, be careful.
There's a thingy right there.
Yeah, see, that's unfortunate.
Here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm protecting...
Lyon.
Look at that!
Pro shit!
The fairway has been cleaned, my lord.
He's happy now, I think.
Um...
There's also a cave over here.
Oh, my god, this place is huge.
What's that?
Giant antlia?
Oh, that's bad, isn't it?
Let's try something funny here.
Boop!
See, that right there is called pro gaming.
Hell yeah, dude.
Don't mess with me.
The most spelunking spelunker that has ever spelunked.
Gimme all of that.
You feel an evil presence watching you.
I don't like that!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Uh...
That's not good.
Put this back here, please.
There was something bad with that.
I remember this.
That is not good.
Will you please get away from me?
Okay, there we go.
Um...
You know what? I have an idea.
If this is gonna appear right here...
Can I put this anywhere?
There.
I'm gonna put some everywhere here.
I'm actually gonna prepare a little bit here.
I don't know if it's gonna appear down here in the cave,
but...
How do I put it?
Wait.
Like this?
Statue.
Oh no!
God damn it!
Make it like here.
Hey! See, that works.
Okay.
You.
Come here.
You fucker.
Wait.
These things are respawning.
That makes me unhappy!
Let me get some buffs going.
What do I have?
I have...
Invisibility?
You know what? Let me equip this
in case I need to get the fuck out of here.
I also want to equip this, actually.
I'm gonna have a party down here.
Everybody! It's a rave!
Oh god.
Look at all the cacti.
It's also dynamite.
You know what?
Maybe nothing will happen down here, actually.
Maybe it's only at my house.
Get away.
Man, that cloud right over there
is doing work.
In fact, I just had a great idea.
I have a great idea!
Check this out!
I'm gonna purposefully do this.
In fact, uh...
And they're gonna be stuck?
Well, almost. And then they get hit by the rain.
No?
Well, it was an idea, I guess.
Wait, no, don't...
Where's my...
Something like that.
Is that enough to stop them?
Okay.
You're there.
Oh god!
Bro, you die quick in this game.
You die really fast.
No, look, we're healing.
I think you're just passive health regen in this game.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Let me try this.
Zoom out.
Fucking just throw these at them.
Look at the skills here, dude.
That's lovely.
Bro, the hook is actually wild.
Okay, uh, zoom in a bit more, here.
What's that? What's that?
Oh, it's nothing.
See you guys.
Where am I going? Where am I going?
I don't even care. I don't even care.
Just go, just go.
Oh my god.
Oh, wait, we're back here now.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
See ya.
Okay, that's pretty cool.
That's a nice little highway we got here.
Damn.
Oh, this is great.
Can you please fall down into that lava?
Thank you.
Okay, let's go the opposite way then.
Ah, hold on.
The best defense.
Get rid of the mine cart.
I'm taking this with me. Apparently nothing happens down here.
That's actually good to know.
So, does that mean there's a huge
fucking thing waiting for me upstairs?
That doesn't sound very good, does it?
Let me keep going this way.
Also, maybe I should start hitting back.
I do have a lot, right?
I feel like I'm getting a little greedy here.
Nah.
No way, dude.
Go this way.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
She's not allowed.
Just dig down, dude.
No, not that way, not that way.
Bro, that's some bullshit.
Why is it rolling the other way?
That doesn't make any sense.
Oh, god.
Damn.
The DPS is great.
Look at it.
It actually shoots super quick when you're close.
Very nice.
Nice.
It's getting a little bit...
I don't know.
Scary.
Dangerous mandible blade.
Wait a second.
I didn't even see I had this.
Oh.
Let's try this out.
Are you there?
I mean, it's sort of dangerous.
Not amazingly dangerous.
Let's try it out for a bit.
Let's see how it goes.
I was looking for my...
Not sand.
Dirt.
No, no, no, no.
Okay, let's try this.
Oh, shit!
Oh, this thing sucks.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That fucking mandible blade is terrible.
Look at the DPS of this here.
Now, that's what I'm talking about.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Oh, why you fucking piece of shit?
That's why you got to clear these things.
No.
Man.
Hold on, didn't I find an item last time
that would put me...
that would allow me to get back
into the cave immediately?
I feel like I read something like that.
Or maybe I'm imagining things.
Uh, quickly.
Quick stack.
Beautiful. And then...
Uh, ores and doors.
Let's put some stuff in here.
Desert fossil?
I feel like that counts as ore.
It's sort of like blocky, tile-y, shapey.
Let's put a bast statue here.
Um...
Let's put one...
Let's put one here.
To watch over.
On each side.
Bast is looking over us, people.
Fear not.
Oh, yeah, I made huge rooms.
I kind of remember this now.
I wanted to separate these so I could have extras.
Maybe I'll quickly do that
before I go back.
Why not, right?
Uh...
That counts as ore, I think.
Dynamite is Michelinius.
Emerald is also ore, I would say.
Yeah.
Definitely.
Now, suspicious looking eye. That's organic, isn't it?
An owl.
I don't have many torches left.
I do, never mind.
I do.
Yellow marigold.
Can be placed.
I wonder if that will grow more
if I do that.
I know these grow trees.
Blink root.
Like this one says can be placed.
These cannot be placed.
These are just material.
Okay.
Man, how do I make potions?
That's like my...
big question right now.
Did I find any bullets?
I don't think so.
Okay.
Um...
We go back.
Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm bringing Abigail.
Increases night vision.
What am I looking for?
Abigail, right.
Just bring it with me. There we go.
Let's go!
Let's go.
Eladon, the traveling merchant has arrived.
Where?
I see you, I see you there.
Let's see what he has.
Eladon.
Let's see more. He really has no
appreciation for a really good deal.
Really?
Is that so?
DPS meter?
This game has...
some items.
Stopwatch?
Display speed?
Sunshine of Israponi.
Bee Witch.
Huh?
Red Dynasty shingles.
A single shingle?
There's a duck somewhere here.
It's messing with me.
Oh, it was up there. I saw it.
It flew away.
Yeah, okay. Fine.
Alright, let's go.
Oh, I thought these were acorns that I...
Have I planted these?
These are not growing.
I can't tell if those are just sticks or...
what should I call it?
Baby trees.
Saplings.
I'm just glad I don't take damage going through these
cacti.
Yeah.
What if I hook onto enemies?
Okay, that doesn't do shit.
I wonder if I can upgrade my item somehow.
This has 22 melee damage.
Very slow speed, which makes no sense,
because it's like hella fast.
So, like...
What?
You know?
What's up, dude?
Yeah, you ain't shit.
You ain't got shit against my...
Celus Harpoon.
Har...
Look, these things are growing, too.
Come up here.
Oh, my God.
Now, that's very effective.
Look at all this crap growing here.
Thank you.
Wait, the good news is now we sort of empty
down our inventory. I forgot to put the lawnmower
in the chest.
Summon the Abigail.
We go right...
This is a long journey, actually.
We went deep.
We are pretty deep in this game.
Something tells me that
the final boss of whatever of this game
is gonna be at the very bottom of the earth.
It's called Terraria, right?
Meaning earth.
So, the goal of the game, I guess,
is to go deeper and deeper.
What is that sound?
Oh, is that Abigail fighting?
Abigail, come back to me.
We have things to do.
That was a bit risky.
Wait, I can just go this way.
This is a bit faster.
Yep, I prefer that.
We've got an enemy.
Then we go down.
Mother's Lime.
It can't even reach me up here.
The hook is so good.
Oh, yeah, right. It spawns smaller ones.
Just grab that.
Further down.
Good.
Okay, we've got a big baddie.
Bastard.
Got you.
Don't even think about it.
Ooh, look at these.
Oh my god.
Why does he change direction?
You fucker.
I guess I went left here.
Let's go.
Maximum speed.
Whoa, did I just drive into him?
Hold on, we've got to take care of this thing.
There we go.
Clean up any hazards.
Wait.
Lion pines, the golfer is still down here.
The minecart.
The minecart is sick.
Shit, how do I...
There.
Stack them up underneath the rain.
And there we go.
Money has been acquired.
We're back. We're back, baby.
I feel like the enemies are gaining more HP.
These enemies are pretty difficult.
Wait, was this where we died?
Yeah, it was.
Okay, okay, we're back.
We are back.
Ooh, I can stop the flow of this completely.
I think these guys are sort of
half immune to fire.
Nice.
What do we got here?
Get rid of that.
Nice. Abigail can take care of those little small creatures.
That's such a nice thing.
I really like that.
Dude, I just remembered. It's fucking Friday.
Let's go!
That makes me so happy.
It's the best feeling ever.
Wait, who's coming?
We have a trap here
that we can utilize.
Oh!
I just destroyed that thing with a single shot somehow.
Oh, god.
Everything's fine.
Skeletons over there.
Man, do I want to... hold on.
I'm scared.
I hear...
This is a bad idea, isn't it?
Holy shit!
We've got dynamite.
What's that up there?
I don't trust it.
Orange blood root.
Used to make orange die.
Okay, gotcha.
Water walking potion!
Wow!
That's awesome.
Cool.
I wonder if that counts with lava as well
if it's like a liquid walking potion
or if it actually just means water.
Hey!
Eladon has departed.
That's fine with me.
I don't care for Eladon anyway.
Taking care of.
Okay.
Yeah, blah, blah, blah.
Oh god.
Everything's fine.
What's that? Amethyst.
Very nice.
Now, can I hit that and take it with me
or...
Is it gonna explode
if I hit it?
Oh man.
I guess we gotta try it for science once, right?
Uh oh.
I just don't want to die right now.
No, I'm not gonna do it.
I'm gonna play safe.
So what the fuck is going on down here?
Look at that over there!
That looks interesting.
I do not want to go down into the lava.
That's a damn fact.
But I will go down here.
Something evil is happening down here.
I see evil.
Come on.
What is that?
Oh, this looks...
This looks dangerous.
Why am I doing this?
What is wrong with me?
Okay, he's dead.
Oh, there's more lava.
You're not careful...
That lava!
There we go.
Wait, what is that?
Oh, it's just the remains
of the thing I just killed.
So I guess the very bottom of the world is like the lava.
That's like the...
the bottom.
That's how they prevent you from going further.
Hey, you're there.
But wait.
There's something going on over there.
Something exciting.
What is that?
I don't know what this is.
I'll take it.
Mmm, delicious.
What is this?
I don't think it...
I can't really loot it.
It seems...
Look for rocks up there.
I don't see any...
Oh!
I took the geyser with me?
The fuck?
Tim!
Tim is here!
What do you think of that?
Hey, Tim.
Fuck you, Tim.
There are some who call them...
Tim?
I guess.
Come here.
Who the fuck is Tim?
Why did he attack me?
I would be friends with him if you wanted,
but, you know...
What did I get?
A wizard hat!
Yo!
Bro!
Ooh, wow!
I was kind of taking the light around me
for granted at this point.
I was kind of taking the light around me for granted at this point.
But I guess the defense is nice.
Maybe that will teach me to put more torches.
Skeleton.
Hey.
Brother.
He's in there now, that's fine.
Oh, I see loot down there.
Also, what is below me?
Lava.
Of course.
I should have known.
Okay.
We're okay.
Okay, I don't want to go that way.
That seems...
I feel like I'm sort of reaching...
You know what? I think it's time to go back.
It's finally time to go back.
What is Abigail fighting?
Oh, the skeleton.
Skeleton.
Good job.
I could go further down, actually.
Let me just go a little further.
Just a bit.
Oh, that's annoying.
Oh, I see loot.
Nice.
Oh, I see pots down there, too.
What is this?
Oh, that's cobweb. Never mind.
Man, I actually do miss the light.
Wait.
Get rid of it!
Okay, you know what?
Here's the thing I need to test on most enemies.
It seems like some of them are immune to fire stuff.
Or like they take way less damage from it, right?
Others not so much.
So I need to test it.
I think I do like this hat more.
Just because of the light.
It's a nice utility to have.
Should I keep digging here?
There's something here. I want to take this.
This is a huge deposit of lead.
And I shall acquire it.
And then I maybe go home.
No, wait. There's not a cave, actually.
This is so...
I just want to keep going, you know?
Fuck it. I'm going to keep going.
My mom's not here to stop me.
I can do whatever the fuck I want.
I will keep going.
Thank you.
Oh, but there's not really anything else going on here.
Is there? Okay, let's...
Fuck it. Let's head back.
Uh, eat the potion.
There it is.
Man, look at all the treasure we brought back.
Oh, yeah.
Why is the bug not a material?
Is it a material because I can use it to craft other things?
Wait, uh...
No, no, no. I need to talk to Dylan.
Hey, Dylan.
You should stay indoors at night.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Actually, help me.
If you had a gun, I bet an arms dealer might show up
to sell you some ammo.
Fucking hell, I would love that.
So we're going to have to expand this house.
But first, let me actually quickly test.
Lava-proof bucket!
But when things get too hot to handle,
Hellstone Bar!
Yeah, that's not happening.
Um, but cool.
Definitely do want to craft that.
Orange blood root can make die.
That makes a lot of sense.
I mean,
why not?
Oh, wait, I, uh...
Wait.
Oh, do I need to be near the...
Which am I called? What's this?
White string?
Increases yo-yo range.
Silk!
I need...
cobweb.
Oh, wait, it's because I'm next to the loom!
That makes fucking sense.
Can I make a bed now?
I needed that for the bed.
Uh...
I need wood for bed, I believe.
Michelinia's construction.
Give me that.
Let's see here.
Bed.
Shit, I actually don't remember what I needed for the bed.
It's over here.
Bed!
Yes!
Tell me I can use it.
Okay, hold on. Um...
Uh, let's put it in one of these rooms.
One of these rooms is going to be my room.
My room is up here, actually.
There's a...
Wait, what's happening? Am I...
So I'm just sleeping, but...
Is time moving faster here or something?
I was really hoping I could skip the night with this.
Let's see if time moves faster.
I...
I think so?
It feels like it's fast.
Maybe... I don't know. Maybe I'm imagining things.
I'm gonna have to try that again later.
When it's proper dark.
Okay, nice.
We've got a wizard hat. You know what?
Can I be a wizard?
I would love to be a wizard.
I want to shoot fireballs and shit.
But then again,
I would love to just shoot guns.
So, let's actually do that.
Let's...
What was this thingy? I need to remember.
Housing.
Wait...
Oh!
Wait.
Hold on. Hold on.
I need to make...
thingies.
This housing is already occupied.
I need to make separate rooms.
That's what I need.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Let's go up here.
And go like this.
Actually,
we need a door, don't we?
Shut up, Seymour!
Doors.
Let's make three...
Two. Two is fine.
So, what I'm gonna do is this.
Door here.
And then, door there.
And then,
we're gonna make more tables.
More chairs, because...
What did I need?
This house is missing a light source and a table.
Right.
Let me make tables.
Two of them...
Let's make...
Yeah, two is fine.
Chairs.
There we go.
And then...
This is a little bit awkward, actually.
Look at this.
I need to fix that.
And then...
Nice.
That's my room.
And then...
Okay, this is actually really annoying.
Hold on, I have an idea.
Let me remove this.
I mean, technically...
I was about to say technically, I don't actually need to have any stairs at all, because I can...
do that.
But, the NPCs can't do anything then.
They can't get up there.
So...
Yikes, maybe I make the other way this time.
Hold on.
That's actually a great idea.
That solves all my problems.
Move.
See, this ain't good.
This ain't good.
There!
Ooh, that's awkward.
I don't know, is that gonna work?
Actually, yeah.
It looks a little bit...
You know?
There it is!
What?
Oh, no, I can't...
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no.
No!
This is painful.
What am I missing wall there?
I don't have wall on me.
Whatever.
Oh, god.
Why is this so...
annoying?
It's a do.
I feel like this is
unnecessarily cumbersome.
To build some dam...
Like, look at this!
What the fuck is this?
Are you kidding me?
Like, why is it...
Why is it doing that?
Do I have to remove all this
every time?
Let's do it like this instead.
No, don't do that.
Oh, it's because this is here.
It's so bad.
There.
Not easy, huh?
And now we can do this.
There it is.
Man, that is...
a catastrophe.
Okay.
Much better.
And then inside of here...
Is there a chair there? I can't tell.
Seamore. Okay, there is...
So, hold on, let's see here.
Oh, but this doesn't count as...
What is this?
Oh, it's wood platform.
We need another table in here.
Let's have the chair there.
Let's see.
I wonder if the chandelier counts.
Let's see here.
This housing is suitable.
Lyon pines the golfer has arrived.
Never mind, he's back somehow.
And he's moved in.
Okay, well...
There it is.
I thought I lost him.
Stop, dude!
You're gonna need a lot of practice.
I strongly recommend padding.
Hold, right.
Wait a minute.
What the fuck, dude?
I'm mowing the lawn.
What if I mow the...
Bunny?
Okay, nothing happened.
Dude, does this actually mean
no monsters will spawn?
That seems awesome,
if that's true.
Mow it all.
It's a little bit awkward to mow
when it's not flat.
Okay, that's nice.
Wait, where's my...
God damn it.
Julia butterfly.
25% bait power.
That's nice.
That's real good.
Lion pines.
Would you mind
coming back with me?
Come on.
There's a room for you.
I prepared it special for you.
Look at that.
We have a wizard hat on that now.
Isn't that lovely?
Wait, did he move into my room?
God, I guess that's fine.
Maybe I don't need a room technically.
Yeah, fuck that.
My room is the whole thing. I am the landlord.
I own everything.
Hope these guys are paying me rent.
Water walking potion.
Dum dum dum.
Oh, I love this feature so damn much.
And now...
Wait.
Oh, was this deposited as well
when I clicked on the button just now?
Nice.
I have 12 gold.
That's frickin' awesome.
Silt block.
Put it in here.
And the geyser is like...
Michelinian, I guess.
Organics.
Potions.
Dum dum dum.
That's also organic.
I can place it.
Do I really want to do this?
That's a terrible idea.
The lawnmower can go into Michelinias for now.
Oh, actually, weapons and tools.
Okay.
So far, things are looking good.
I do want to separate this as well, actually.
Do we have a...
Looks like all the rooms are actually occupied.
Dylan, wait.
Do we really have that many people?
Wait, Ludo the painter?
Who the fuck are you?
Hello?
Rain is my worst nightmare.
It literally rinses out all my hard work.
Happiness.
I don't like all these people around making noise
when I'm painting.
Why don't I like the forest?
Because it's boring.
Green, brown, that's it.
Huh.
Is he telling me that he wants to live somewhere else?
Shop.
Paint roller.
Oh.
I can color the walls.
Dude, this game gets deeper and deeper.
All the time.
Game.
Hold on.
Let me make a room in here.
You know what? Let's remove this.
The living loom.
I wonder if this counts as a table. Hold on.
What is that even? That's the workbench.
Do I have another? I have another one over there.
Let me put this...
Actually, let me put this back here.
I want to try something.
I want to see if that actually counts as a table.
Let's make a chair.
Ooh, I can also...
Bar stool.
Ooh, man. Bar.
Banquet. Hold on now.
I want to make a bar.
Bar.
And I want to make a bar stool.
Let me try something.
What if I...
Let's have the bar down here.
I'm going to have a bar in here.
Let's see.
Hey!
Wait, no, no, no. Get off.
I get to sit on this.
Now.
Oh, but wait. This is here.
So...
Let me remove this for a second.
Does this still count?
I think it does.
Look at this. This counts as a room now.
Let me do this now.
Then another door, please.
Let's just make a couple.
There.
Okay.
And then in here, I can put
these now.
Let's test this.
Does that work?
This house is missing a light source.
Oh, right.
And that's all?
This housing is suitable.
Okay, cool. That actually counts.
But I don't want to put it there.
I want to put it...
there.
Look at this. It's starting to look like something.
I mean, people don't... it's like the bearer essentials, I guess.
It's going to be nice in time.
Yep.
We can even make a room up here.
Like a very scuffed room.
What is a very thin... can I have a very
narrow table, maybe?
You feel an evil presence watching you?
Oh, no.
Hold on. Should I be preparing here?
Last time I didn't have any healing.
Uh...
Wait.
Give me this.
Put...
Construction. Put this in here.
Pink vase.
What potions do I have?
Let's drink that.
And...
Let's...
Summon that.
Oh god, here we go.
I think things are about to happen.
We got to be ready.
Let me go over here, actually.
Let me go away from the house.
Oh, wait, wait.
We need the best statue. No, wait, we have them up here.
Oh, wait, wait, I have an idea.
This thing is able to go through walls, right?
Uh...
Oh, that's actually really bad.
That's actually really bad.
Give me this.
Let me go over here.
Oh, fuck, here we go.
Ah! Where are you?
Oh god.
Kill it!
Oh, Jesus.
Get inside the house.
Come on, people, help me fight this thing.
I got a heal.
Oh, hey, we're doing decent damage here.
Oh god.
Oh, that's scary.
No, no, no, no, no, we're leaving.
I need to heal.
Oh!
Bro!
Oh, there's no way I can heal in time.
What the fuck are you supposed to do?
Against that.
Jesus!
Okay, well, that was kind of close.
We almost had them.
Not bad.
I wonder why that happens.
What triggers that thing?
Oh, people have lost HP here.
That's bad.
Okay, that went better than last time.
We're making progress at least.
Okay, well, let's calm down.
Let's calm down.
Let me try the bed.
It's night now.
What happens?
Yeah, look at the time. Look at the cloud.
It's definitely moving faster.
Look at the clouds in the background.
I'm just chilling on the bed.
I can even check out my inventory while I do this.
Also, I should be going...
All in star.
I want to go in some random direction now.
When the day starts,
it's time to...
What the hell is happening down there?
The zombies are coming.
Man, the night is long, huh?
Maybe I don't want to sleep all night.
Fuck it, we're going.
We're going right now.
I guess this is a nice way to test.
See, there's no enemies right here.
Grass grows, though.
Can I not...?
Ah, there we go.
I'm just going to keep going east now.
I wonder if the auto-select
will work on the worm.
What's that?
Hold on.
Are these leftovers from the fight just now?
Man, there's enemies everywhere.
Just keep going.
Let's go.
Can I take this with me?
What did I get?
Water leaves. Water leaves seeds.
Nice.
Just eat that mushroom.
This guy is ascending to the moon.
Okay, that's annoying.
Stupid enemies.
Okay, we're going on a massive journey to the east now.
We're going to the edge of the world.
Can I destroy it with this? Oh yeah, nice.
No, don't go down there. Keep going up.
Clear a path.
Coming through. Hot soup.
Man, this is treacherous terrain.
I need to find some...
I don't want to use my healing potions.
But I am regen-ing, so that's fine.
Wait, am I regen-ing because of some item I have, actually?
That's why I'm regenerating.
Of course.
It makes sense.
Deathweed.
I totally forgot I got that item.
Clear it all.
Just keep going east.
I'm so tempted to go in these caves.
But I am restraining myself.
Ow, that hurt.
Oh my god. Oh, this is dangerous.
Kill him!
Holy shit, that was scary.
Oh, here we go.
Umbrella!
Wait!
That's a weapon.
Take it all.
I need to test that out.
Let's try.
Oh, that's actually pretty cool.
I like that.
That's pretty nice.
Okay, keep going up.
Shit, it's kind of hard to get up there.
Just keep going this way then.
I guess it is raining, right?
Let's rock the umbrella for a bit.
It's raining blood.
Hey!
Umbrella fight!
Let's go!
I dare you. I double dare you, motherfucker.
I mean, I guess these enemies will just keep coming.
There's no reason to...
Eladon is back as well.
God, it's so difficult to hit with this thing sometimes.
I hate enemies.
Okay.
Oh, this is nice.
Nice.
Look at this.
Oh, it's also day now. That's so beautiful.
Exactly what I need.
No more monsters.
Throwing knives. Wood.
Silver. Nice.
And grenades. That's lovely.
Wand of sparking!
Yo, hold on.
Oh!
Is that consuming?
Wait.
Uses two mana.
Shoots a small spark.
I'm actually casting spells.
Oh, God.
I'm fucking dying.
Oof.
Why am I not losing mana?
Am I regenning so quickly?
Oh, yeah, I am.
The umbrella.
Hard radar.
Yo, that's better than the normal radar.
I'll take it.
This is a material as well. We can use this to craft things, it seems.
Bottles? Yes, dude!
Maybe I can make potions now.
Burn!
No, this one sucks.
It's such a slow projectile.
And that gives me mana now.
That's interesting.
I'm preferring my normal weapons here.
I gotta be honest.
Don't go down into the cave!
We want to continue moving on.
What's that?
Flying fish?
Get out of here.
Glow sticks?
Grazie.
That was empty.
Bombs!
Nice.
Keep going, east.
What do we got over here?
Watch this again.
Yellow marigolds.
Ooh, this is steep.
That's okay.
We're fine.
Yo, what's this?
What, a wood trunk?
How do I...
Cool.
Gives me wood.
I mean, I'll take it.
What's that?
Man, look at this area.
This is so quaint.
Love all the water.
That's so nice.
We're going far away from...
Do we have potions of return?
We do.
What's that?
Jungle bat!
Sugar cane!
No, bamboo.
That's probably nice as well.
It's a material. We can use it to craft things.
Lots of healing potions.
Man, I...
Ooh!
I want to go down into the cave.
I'm restraining myself.
What the fuck?
What is Abigail doing?
What is this weapon doing?
Okay, there's something going on there, but...
You fucker.
Umbrella hat!
I mean, that's exactly what I expected.
Sir, are you okay down here?
What's happening?
Need some assistance?
There, water.
Okay, you know what? Maybe I'll quickly check out what's down here.
Did I just get some HP?
There was some kind of HP item.
Dude, this is so much fun.
I love exploring.
Bombs!
Whoa! That was a whole gold!
That's crazy!
I feel like these enemies or these slimes here are...
Wait.
Why was I being pushed to the left there just now?
These slimes are a little bit more difficult than usual.
Nice.
Abigail, come on. We're moving.
Look at this waterfall.
Oh, we've got a little bit of a cave.
Not much of a cave, though.
There we go.
What are we gonna find?
Look at the background.
Very wooded.
What the hell is that?
Some kind of plant.
Alright, don't go down there.
Nice. Let me put this here.
Just so I remember.
This looks like a tree. Is this a beehive?
Uh-oh.
Yeah. Knew it.
A sluggy!
Aw, I didn't want to kill it. Damn it.
Okay.
Ooh, we've got a bit of a cave here.
A chest!
Another umbrella.
Why not? Does it stack?
No.
25% increased movement speed. 8 minutes.
That is an insane potion.
I would love to have that during the fight.
With a big eye.
That sounds like a good time.
That was like my issue.
I couldn't move around very much. It was too fast for me.
Okay.
Give me all of this good stuff.
Okay, nice.
Recall potion. Nice.
And bombs.
Look at all these items here.
This is lovely.
I want to set fire to the beehive.
Boo!
Didn't work like I thought it would.
Okay. Do I want to go down here?
Nah.
I want to keep moving right.
I am tempted.
Wait, there's a chest here.
Another umbrella.
I think I just skipped that umbrella for now.
In fact...
You will...
Hold on.
I don't know what to bring.
Let's throw this away.
The cobweb can go away as well, I guess.
Nice. Oh, is it night already?
How the fuck?
I feel like it just became day.
No, Abigail.
Okay, we are going to kill this actually.
Let's heal up.
Wow, see the zombies are...
Wait, why am I so slow?
What?
Hold on, something's going on.
It causes...
Sometimes when I move left, my character moves right.
I can't tell if that's in-game stuff.
Or if it's my fucking keyboard messing up here.
Very awkward.
Come on, kill it.
I'm being bamboozled.
Get rid of these? Oh, God.
I'm actually low HP here.
Put a torch.
Fuck you.
See, I guess fire is really good against plants.
Because duh, right?
What is this?
Can I actually take these plants with me?
Oh, God.
Enemy's everywhere.
Yeah, see, I need to break these pots.
That's what gives me HP in this game.
I'm almost dying.
Kill this fool.
Oh, my God.
I'm taking so much damage unnecessarily, I feel like.
But I'm definitely going on an adventure here.
Nice.
Give me that HP.
I need to heal. Real bad.
I need to... Oh, my God.
Oh, I think I may die.
Maybe not, maybe not, maybe we're fine.
Heal up.
Man, being out during the night is rough.
Shit.
Just keep moving.
Oh, yeah, heal.
I may not survive much longer here.
I need to make an emergency shelter.
Fuck, I...
I can't right here.
Fuck you!
Okay, chillax.
Okay.
Abigail, take care of them.
I need to heal up for a second here.
What do I have?
I have a bunch of healing potions, actually.
Now, could I make them into better ones?
Wait, enchanted nightfall?
Star in a bottle.
Ah, campfire.
There we go.
How much faster?
Oh, that's significant.
Now we're talking.
Come on, guys.
Man, Abigail is fucking owning.
Look at this!
Yeah.
This feels real good.
Oh, my God.
I'm owning.
That's how you do it.
Let's destroy some shit.
Yeah, I should destroy that.
And I guess we can destroy this as well.
I just...
Honestly, these are the same.
Destroy one of them.
Oh, God.
Okay, we're fine.
This one needs to be on a keybind for me.
This is some expedition.
I mean, look at this. We're farming gold.
We are making bank.
And we're just gaining general...
combat experience, you know, with the game.
It's kind of important. Actually, there's a cave right here, too.
Uh-oh.
And it's day now.
So this is the time to...
You know what, actually?
You should go caving during the night
and exploring on the surface during the day.
See, that makes the most sense.
Do I really want all this tin? I don't even think I do.
Give me all that money.
Thank you.
That's awesome.
And now we keep moving.
Oh, thank you.
Definitely feeling way more mobile
than I did in the beginning of this game.
It feels good.
Okay, we got a star.
I keep thinking, oh man, I don't know if I should keep going
because it's so far from home, but I have the potion of return,
so everything is fine.
I'm just super worried.
Wonderful.
This one sucks.
Zombie banner?
Man, I hate that I don't want to...
Can I make a backpack or something?
Delete this.
Let's delete the water leaf as well.
The death... deathweeds?
How about we delete the wood platforms?
We have wood anyway.
Mod blocks can get deleted.
Lens can get... I have a bunch of those anyway.
I think that's fine.
Sure, these are not that great, are they?
But I can sell them, I guess.
I wonder how much they're worth.
I'm gonna have to check that.
We've got a big-ass cave.
And chests.
Guide to the plant fiber cordage.
Allows the collection of vine rope from vines?
It's one of these.
Violent depth meter.
Sure.
Yeah, I don't want this right now anyway.
This is a material, by the way. We can use this to craft something else.
I need to ask Dylan about this.
A can of worms!
Should I open this?
I got seven worms.
I don't know what I expected.
Of course.
I get worms out of that.
Makes total sense.
Okay, take- ooh!
Mining potion!
Bro!
25%?
Isn't that kind of nuts?
I feel like that's nuts.
What's that?
Look at this little cave here.
Enchanted sword.
Get rid of...
gel.
23!
Shoots an enchanted sword beam.
Now that sounds interesting.
Whoa!
Oh wait, it's costing.
Wait.
What is the bleep- bleep sound?
Oh, I think that means
it's when the thing is recharged
and that's when you have the projectile again.
That's what that means.
Whoa!
That's not bad.
But I need further testing though.
Oh right, I need this for that.
Oh, I don't want this end, actually.
Oh, we're now in a different biome.
Ooh, listen to this music.
Seashells.
Oh my god, there's so many things I want to get.
I don't know what to get rid of.
Fuck!
Let's remove the glow sticks
and I guess... consumable?
Fuck the frogs.
Fuck the water leaf seeds
and the deathweed.
Vine rope.
Get rid of that.
Plus three range.
Ten oar.
The throwing knives.
I kind of want to see if I can sell those for something.
Sleeping angler!
Thanks, I guess, for saving me or whatever.
You'd be a great helper minion.
How dare you, sir?
Tell me about happiness.
I'm a kid.
You need to give me a house. Are you dumb?
Yes. I get to be alone with all my fish.
Why is the ocean my favorite place to go?
It has tons of cool fish.
Duh!
Well... oh, quest?
Out in the forest I was fishing, right?
Well, guess what?
A bunny hopped up to me.
Then another one hopped up and another.
Suddenly I'm surrounded by bunnies.
One even swam up to me from the water.
But it had no legs.
I fell out of my chair in surprise
and all the bunnies scurried off.
I want that bunny fish as a pet.
So you better catch it for me.
Pronto!
Caught in surface.
Bunny fish.
Okay, um...
Sure.
I shall catch you a...
Bunny fish.
Ooh, that's a lot of water. Is it down here?
Wait, do you need me to fish for it?
Can I...
find it like this?
Whoa!
This is deep!
Hold on now.
How do I make it across here?
Wait.
Can I make a...
You know what?
I have an idea.
Make this.
Scorpion.
No, I don't want that.
Let me try this.
Uh...
In fact, put this here for...
Let's have a little outpost here.
A little nice outpost.
Get rid of this stupid tree.
I'm sorry, Scorpion!
I apologize.
And now...
Now we go fishing.
Do we have any debate?
How does this work again?
No!
Is that...
Oh yeah, I think it's working.
I wouldn't create.
No way.
What's in it?
Oh.
Quick climbing claws.
Allows the ability to slide down walls?
Improve the ability if combined with shoe spikes.
Bro!
Yo!
That sounds awesome!
Fuck the book!
I want this!
Hold on, you know what?
Bro!
I just had the greatest idea
how to save space!
Can I put the bug net somewhere here?
No.
Oh my god, I'm genius.
What else can I put there?
Listen to the seagulls.
This is nice.
Yo, can I...
Wait a minute.
Wait, social accessory.
Does this go anywhere here?
Why being...
I'm just testing things right now.
Uh...
Let's sort the item.
Seagull!
A seagull.
Seagull, come here.
Hop!
You belong to me now.
It's consumable.
A sea turtle!
You belong...
You do not belong to me now.
Um...
No!
We also have this one.
Um...
There's nothing else I can equip, right?
Wait a minute.
If I go...
Wait, what is block swap?
Oh, is it just...
If I go like...
No, wait.
I'm not sure what that is.
Whatever.
Crap!
Get out of here.
Okay, uh...
Let's do some fishing, huh?
Let's do it.
So it says 8 here?
Because I have 8 baits somewhere.
A trout!
Let me just test that with the bait here.
I have 8 baits.
Yeah, look.
Beautiful stuff.
Also, it shows it on my cursor.
Look.
I just noticed.
Nice.
Dude, I want to find more crates.
God damn!
This looks so...
Oh, here we go!
A swiftness potion.
I'll take it. Thank you.
I need more.
It's so nice.
We have the seagull.
We have a little campfire, a little table.
And look at the distance. There's islands.
I like this.
Ah, man.
What a great Friday.
Here's trouting along.
I do wonder if I can make a boat.
Just a tiny raft, maybe.
Tuna.
Now we're talking.
Man, I can't wait to show Dylan
everything I've found.
He's not going to believe it.
My god, there's a dolphin too now.
Dolphin.
You're mine.
Oh my god!
There's a cool flip!
Well done, dolphin.
Dolphin?
Oh, I thought he was killing the dolphin.
Let me help you.
This crap is a menace to society.
Why can't I...
Oh, it's because I'm using
the other loadout.
Hold on. What did I key bind that as?
I need to remember this.
I don't want to look...
What's it?
Hold on, I'm going to...
Whoops.
I'm going to use...
Was it this one? It was!
No, wait.
There it is. Look.
That's the key bind for that.
I do...
I kind of like having the head on.
The stupid head on while we fish.
Maybe I'll have like a fishing loadout.
You know?
Something cozy.
Also, what did that guy want again?
He want the bunnyfish.
A shrimp, poh boy!
Poh boy, are you in for a treat?
Really?
How did I get that?
Come on.
Gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
Also, I just noticed we only have five...
Wait, we only have four...
Oh, maybe every successful fish attempt.
You lose one.
Wait, no, no.
Look, wait.
There? No, wait.
Okay, maybe it's just random.
So we have four now.
Let me see if I can figure this out.
Getting lots of trouts though.
We're going to have a feast later.
Look at the stars.
The stars are coming out.
This is so cozy.
Okay, yeah. See, there we lost one.
Yeah, it's random.
Bomb fish!
I wonder if I throw this in the ocean
and will they swim before they explode?
Nope.
Definitely not.
Would be cool though.
Come on.
I think maybe it's two times ahead of home.
But I kind of want to find
the bunnyfish
before I go.
I'm going to have to go talk to that guy.
Oh, here we go.
Switch load out.
There we go.
That worked pretty well.
Shot out of the water.
Okay.
Is this dude over here?
Wait, where'd he go?
My dude?
Did he die?
I hope he didn't die.
You fucker, you better not die.
Maybe he went back to the base.
Just like the other guy.
Okay, you know what? I'm going to head back.
It's time.
Where's the thingy?
Wait, am I blind?
There it is.
Perfect.
Let's remove this.
We don't want to see that.
We should be mowing some lawns here.
Izzy!
He did go back. Perfect.
Hey, just to sacrifice...
I mean, competent fishing master
that I've been looking for.
Tell me about the quest again.
Out in the forest, I was fishing, right?
Well, guess what?
A bunny? Yeah, okay.
I fell on my chair and surprised
in all the bunnies.
I want that bunnyfish in the forest.
So I need to be in the forest, I guess.
Maybe that's what it is.
First of all,
we click on this button.
Look at that.
That is the best feature ever.
I cannot get over how brilliant that is.
Organics? Okay. Oh, Dylan!
Dylan!
You should stay. Yeah, shut up.
Help me!
You should prove yourself by the... Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know what? You're not helping.
I want to try to
make things, Dylan.
Can you help me?
With a tulip shell.
A shell pile.
And that requires heavy workbench.
Don't I have that right here?
Am I not in range?
I'm not. Okay.
Wait, wouldn't beam?
Hold on a sec.
What is this?
Oh, it's background!
Oh, it's aesthetic!
Oh, that's not bad at all.
I like that a lot.
Not bad.
Cool stuff. Flaming arrow.
Let's...
Let's make as many as we can of those.
Why the hell wouldn't we?
Yeah. Amazing.
Is this the heavy workbench?
Ah, here we go. Shell pile.
Sure, just make those.
What else can I make here?
Pomwood sword.
No.
Bamboo lantern.
Wait.
That looks like a desk lamp.
Hell yeah!
I've got upgrades!
Look at this, people!
What do you think of that?
That's awesome.
What else can I make?
Pomwood? Sure, let's do it.
Pomwood.
That's for you, even though you're a brat.
You get it.
That's for you.
Very nice.
I'm upgrading everything for the people.
Cooked fish.
Minor improvements to all stats.
Roasted bird is also minor.
So shime is pretty good.
We have a pomwood candle.
Pomwood chair.
This looks like an office chair.
Decorative healing potion.
What else can I try?
Dylan, we need to talk.
Yeah!
Dylan, tell me about this.
Here we go.
Apple juice.
So it looks like all the
hashtag food
in this game
is mostly just
stat improvements. It doesn't actually heal you.
Which is something I was hoping for,
like the mushroom.
Maybe the main type of healing in this game
is just simply the potion.
Pinaculada.
If you like pinaculadas and getting caught in the rain.
Is this a reference to Shrek?
I feel like it is.
Tropical smoothies.
Holy shit. Wait a minute. What's this?
Hold on.
Crafting window.
Dragonfly jars?
What about potions though?
Oh, here we go.
Reduced potion cooldown.
Oh shit. Required objects
bottle.
Wait, I mean, yeah.
Obviously.
Gel, bottle, and mushroom.
Wait a minute.
I have mushroom.
Do I have gel on me right now?
Wait a minute.
Organics?
Where did I put it?
Michelin is probably.
Oh, you have a shit ton of gel.
And bottle. I have everything.
So I should be able to make it right now, no?
No.
Crafting.
Then I need to give you the bottle.
What did you say?
Bottle?
Wait, do you mean like a physical object?
God, I cannot figure out my inventory.
Holy shit.
Oh, my bottle is here.
Okay, let me try this.
Like that?
Wow, that was obscure.
The fuck?
That's...
That's very obscure.
Holy shit.
But I did it.
Heck yeah.
And now.
Dylan.
Blowing mushroom.
I have a bunch of that, don't I?
Mushroom.
Teal.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Heck yeah.
Oh, look at this.
Oh, this is big.
This is big.
And then.
What if I give you this now?
Oh, wait.
Oh, that's it, huh?
You can't go further than...
in other recipes there.
Shell pile?
What is the point of shell pile?
It can be placed.
Oh.
It's like...
some kind of decorative...
thing?
I'm guessing that's like construction then.
Let's put that in there.
Bamboo.
Let's test that out.
Dylan, tell me about the bamboo, huh?
Oh, it's most of the things I already know about.
Bamboo chest.
Oh, you know what would be really cool?
To have a specifically designed look
for every chest that contains
different categories of materials.
So let's say you have organics, right?
It would be in a bamboo chest.
It's easy to see immediately what is what.
And you don't need to mouse over it
to see the name.
Would be pretty cool.
We can even have mushroom platforms
if we want to.
Okay, Dylan, is there anything else
you can tell me about my goodies?
Flowing mushroom?
It's an aura of light.
That's actually pretty neat.
Day bloom.
And bottled water.
Mushroom campfire life.
Is that just the same as the normal?
Let's see here.
Mushroom wall.
Mushroom toilet.
I don't know about that.
That does not sound too good, does it?
Now, Dylan, we need to
look at the bottles again here.
Bottled water.
Oh, you don't need anything
other than a bottle.
That makes sense, I guess.
Sort of.
Let's just do that.
Wait.
Why doesn't that work?
Dylan, what did you...
Hold on.
Bottled water.
Required objects. Water!
Okay.
That makes total sense. We got to be next to some water.
Gotcha.
Now, the trout.
Dylan, tell me about the trout.
Cook. Yeah, right.
You know what? Let's make all this, actually.
And then sell it.
The tulip shell.
What about this?
Sticky dirt.
No, no, no, no. Don't want that.
But, wait a minute.
There were some items that I remember wanting to check.
This is a material.
Shoot a little frost.
Ice torch.
Wait, can I put anything?
190?
Whoa, hold on.
Mithril Anvil required.
And I need to make...
Wait, does this require all of these?
No way.
Holy shit.
That's crazy.
What about this?
Bro, that's insane.
Oh, Bucknit. Oh, yeah, that was that one.
This one?
Seagull statue. Seagull cage.
I don't know if I want to cage a seagull.
That sounds mean.
What's this?
Poisoned knife.
Requires no objects.
Well, that's a fucking lie.
Are you lying to me, Dylan?
Fuck, where is it?
I legitimately cannot find them.
The things I just looked at.
Huh?
I give up.
I must be completely blind.
I don't understand.
Oh, there they are.
My goodness.
Ah, we even need vicious powder. Okay.
Sure.
Vicious powder.
Very weird.
No, actually put the other one.
I want to play with this one a bit more.
I can't put this in there.
Can I put this in here?
No.
It needs to say material, I think.
What about some good old dirt?
All kinds of...
So the vanity stuff
is
interesting.
Is that related to this stuff over here?
Is that like my housing
outfit, so to speak, my casual attire?
Hold on.
Actually, I can test that.
Wait a minute.
Wasn't this...
Wait.
This is vanity. Can I...
Why am I...
Wait a minute.
I was expecting this only
to be equipped in the house.
Maybe this is just like
the cosmetic layer on top
of your stat layer,
if that makes sense.
So you have a stats, and then
you have your cosmetics.
Yo, that's actually
pretty cool.
I like that system.
That's not bad.
Very nice.
Also, didn't I have a
certain thingy?
Did I leave it up there?
I have an idea.
Let's just hang this shit.
We're gonna have the ultimate
stat buffs
when we're at home.
Palmwood.
Delete it!
That's what I say.
You know what, actually?
Look at this. It's here now.
It's still here, right? Until you replace it.
So this is actually an extra inventory
slot in a pinch.
Right?
You can totally use it
like that. You gotta be careful, though, of course.
Now, let me sell some shit.
Izzy, do you want to buy maybe?
Wait, you don't sell anything.
See more.
I feel like an evil presence is watching me.
Uh...
I felt the same, dude!
What up?
That ain't good, though.
Oh, I...
Oh, I could actually have bought these from him.
I didn't even realize.
Fuckin' it.
That was the collection of hay from grass!
Hold on a second, now!
I'll try that.
Uh...
Okay. Buy my shurikens, please.
How much are you willing to pay?
That's not bad.
What about...
I'll take that as well.
That's for you.
Okay.
I wonder if there's an enchanting system in this game.
Let's put stuff in the piggy bank.
Ah, no!
Shit.
Wait. Dude, I have a shit ton of money.
Look at this.
20?
Put this in here.
Put this in the piggy bank!
Uh...
Sure.
Now, what else do I have here, actually?
Let's try the sapphire.
Let's actually do some more asking Dylan.
This is...
I call this game Ask Dylan.
Criminetine ore?
We can make more crimetine bars, I guess.
Now, amber.
I was curious about that.
That's what fossil I'm curious about.
This I'm curious about.
Also...
I am curious about sand!
In fact, I'm passionate about sand.
Sand block.
Silt I'm...
Medium...
Passionate.
Not as much as sand, but...
They say there is a...
Shut up. Help me.
I want to spend a stylist.
Shut off. Yeah, okay, so I can find someone else there.
Um...
Tell me about the silt.
Okay, I've asked you before.
Sand block?
Glass!
Magic sand dropper?
What do you mean?
Requires an...
Wait, is this like a pipette?
What is that?
Empty dropper.
Looks like a pipette.
What?
Uh...
Oh, really?
Let's make a bunch of this.
And then...
Dylan.
Look at this glass I made.
Ooh, here we go!
Oh my goodness!
That's how we make bottles, of course!
Mugs.
Glass sink!
Bath tops.
Video visage.
Huh? Equipable?
Whoa!
What do you mean, equipable?
What?
Honey clock.
Bro, we're making...
Oh, we are making bottles.
Uh, what do I need to make it?
Furnace.
Oh, we are making bottles.
Oh, here we go, dude.
Yes!
Yeah!
Wait, I have an idea.
Quick test. How does this look in the game?
Thank God you can destroy the glass and get it back.
Let me remove this for a second.
Why does this take so long?
I'm going to see if I can make a window.
Is this just going to work like this?
Whoops.
Whoa.
I mean, yeah, it works.
Look!
That's a window.
And then...
She's thinking about fighting on the beach.
It seems.
What did I destroy here?
Did I have a bowl up here?
Silt blocks.
Let's leave this and that one too.
I don't want it.
Okay, that's cool.
Now.
Let's talk about...
this here.
Amber.
Wait, amber hook?
What is the point of this?
Is this just cosmetics?
Or does it actually have an effect on something?
I had some kind of different hook last time as well.
Increases chance to get a crate?
Oh, man, it requires all kinds of things.
Oh.
Gym lock.
Orange face blade.
Oh, man, I really want to craft some of this shit.
Okay, okay.
Fine.
Crimson.
Crimson bar.
Emerald.
What's this?
Green face blade.
It all requires meteorite bars, it seems.
Emerald hook.
Is that what I made last time?
I made some kind of hook out of a material.
Green torch.
For capture the gym.
This is... I'm not sure what this is.
Maybe that's a multiplayer thing.
Okay, I'm curious about this, Dylan.
You won't tell me anything?
Wait, wait, wait. I'm going to test something now.
Tell me I still have my...
Dart trap. Let's try this.
Wait, is this...
Hold on a second. That's not optimal.
Wait, what? Oh, Dylan!
Dylan!
Tell me...
about this real quick.
Can I make like a wall version of this?
I definitely can!
And it's called glass wall...
Wait, I need a workbench.
Hell yeah, dude!
That's exactly what I was looking for.
There we go.
Thank you.
Oh, look!
Oh, that looks way better, too, actually.
Oh, look! Oh, that's not good.
That's not good.
Look at that.
Oh, it's so much better, too.
I don't have to remove the blocks first.
I love that. That's nice.
Have a couple windows there.
Have a nice big window here.
Look at that!
This looks a little bit messy, actually.
That's a nice window, isn't it?
Oh, you can even see through it, actually.
That's nice.
These windows are too small. I don't like these windows.
I'm gonna have to rethink this.
This house is a mess.
We're experimenting here.
This is all one big experimento, friendo.
Quick stack.
Sure.
And let's deposit some stuff.
The weapons...
Maybe I should...
You know what? The flaming maze
has been very good to me.
I'm gonna keep it.
I'm gonna wear it while wearing this.
Yeah.
And...
Yeah. Yep.
That's good.
I can make some more healing potions,
I believe.
So, let's do that.
We need to be next to this bottle.
Oh, man. How was it again?
Gel.
Right.
Damn gel.
Wait, do I not have it on me already?
Oh, I have it on me.
Was it like a flower or something?
I forgot already.
Shit.
Bottle, gel, and owl mushroom.
Right.
I don't have any more of those,
unfortunately, unless...
not really.
Well, I do want to try all of these
as well with Dylan.
Brother.
Oh, this sword
is pretty sick.
Give me these stars.
Look at all the stars!
Okay, that's it.
Okay.
I think it's time
to put some stuff in chest
and then head out again.
Actually, I'm going to go try
and see if I can't find
that fish, the bunny fish.
I'm going to take my amazing fishing pole.
Oh, wait, I was testing this thing.
Let me do that real quick.
Let's say I put it...
Ah, shit.
Ah, there.
And then...
Let me get rid of this real quick.
Maybe I need that
pressure plate.
Can I leave it up here?
Michelinius, I guess.
Brown pressure plate.
What's this?
Enchanted Nightcrawler.
Yoink!
Wait.
Is that what I just got?
That's not a Nightcrawler.
That's a Firefly.
Oh!
35% bait power.
Cool.
Okay, so let's try this now.
What if I put it right next to it?
Maybe it needs to be below.
Wait, active stone block.
Maybe it doesn't shoot when I walk on it.
Maybe it's only for enemies.
But then I would need more of those active stone blocks.
Yeah, I have no clue.
Let's just wait with that.
It was worth it to try it, at least?
It total...
I was so sure this was going to be some kind of redstone.
Equivalent.
Crème tain.
Let's see what I can actually make at the furnace.
Let me grab these.
Star and a bottle.
Oh wait, I can make these.
Oh!
Yeah, sure. Let's make a bunch.
Not bad.
Let's make these as well.
Cool.
Wait, can I make...
Oh, why would I want to do that?
That doesn't make any sense.
Firefly and a bottle?
Let's try it.
Hey, who wants a firefly?
Wouldn't that fit with the living table here?
That's...
Oh, it hangs!
Oh, that's so nice!
Does this count as a light?
I think it does.
Also, I need to make more rooms.
Running of space here.
Everyone's joining the party.
Where's my ammo guy, though?
When is this guy going to come?
That's what I want to know.
Damn.
Okay, sword first.
Sword inventory.
And then...
Quick...
Back...
Hold on.
Nice.
Michelinius.
Put some sticky bombs in there.
The trout organic.
Put the bombfish in here.
Ah, that's more like...
Michelinius, isn't it?
Mushroom.
I think inventory management
is my ultimate weakness in video games.
It's just confirmed.
I mean, I...
I am so terrible at it.
I wonder if anyone else has this much trouble
with inventory.
Or if it's just me.
That's what I want to know.
Put the umbrella in there.
I don't want it.
I want to try the sickle.
So, iron skin.
Eight defense. That's kind of insane.
Oh!
I'm so dumb!
That's how I'm going to cross the ocean!
The water walking potion!
I didn't even occur to me!
More doors.
Wait, I didn't try the desert fossil one.
With Dylan, I'm going to try that.
Destruction.
I have so many recall potions.
Alright, this looks fine.
This looks good.
The desert torch, though? Nah.
Not feeling it.
What?
Is Dylan into Hanno?
What's happening here?
Greetings, Oliver. Is there something I can help you with?
Yes, please help me.
If Seymour's wares don't interest you,
a wandering merchant often visits with exotic merchandise.
You might prefer.
Yeah, I know.
But I'm too poor!
Tell me about this here desert fossil.
I can make desert fossil wall.
Why not?
Requires workbench and ectomist.
Huh?
Wait, I can't make that, I guess.
That goes in the chest for now.
Looks like a...
doors and doors for now.
Okay then.
It's time.
We're gonna head back east.
And while we do it,
I'm gonna see if I can find something.
Man, this looks so neat.
I'm loving this little design up here.
That's so cool.
This is probably not gonna work.
I think it needs to be a certain size.
But I know there's a...
a spot to the right here somewhere.
Oh, but wait, now we're in the desert.
Let's go west instead.
Let's see if we can't find a pool of water there.
Oh, my goodness.
Get away from me.
Man, I'm...
Look at this fucking house.
I'm actually ha... who are you?
Ludo, right.
I'm happy about how this looks so far.
It's not bad, is what I'm saying.
Close the door.
Actually, you know what?
We've been going for three and a half hours.
I'm gonna take a break here.
I'm gonna eat some food, maybe like a 15 minute break.
Because I wanna keep playing this game, man.
I'm feeling it.
So I will be...
going away for a bit.
15 minutes or so.
I'm gonna make a countdown.
So, yeah.
People, go visit the toilet and all that.
And do your things.
Get some snacks and we'll be back, okay?
I'm gonna make a neat transition here.
Hold on.
Can I...
If I click here, the game is paused.
Beautiful.
So, I'll see you on the other side, people.
Yeah.
Hey, everybody.
Actually, before I continue,
real quickly.
Two things.
Is the audio still good?
Second thing, is the chat placement better now?
Is it blocking anything?
Has it blocked anything yet?
I saw there was a boss
health bar at some point.
And I'm not sure if it blocked that.
Both are good.
Nice.
Chat is caught off on the bar.
Wait, are you joking?
Chat cuts off?
Well, it's supposed to cut off.
I'm not sure what you mean.
Hold on.
Let me see here.
Chat cuts off at the bottom.
Not joking? Okay.
Hold on.
See if I can fix that.
Oh, yeah.
Like, does it cut off the text?
Or does it just cut off one line of chat?
Oh, but that...
Okay, well...
Yeah, I'm not sure I can do anything about that.
Actually.
Yeah, I can't do anything about that.
Has it not always been like this?
I haven't really changed anything.
Hmm.
Moving the chat. No, no, look.
This is the whole thing right here.
Like, there's nothing else down below.
I can only crop up.
I can't crop further down. It's like...
It's so weird.
I think maybe it's a bug on YouTube.
Yeah.
Okay.
Alright.
Oh, wait.
From now on, chat is one-liners only.
Oh, really?
Wait, I have an idea.
Maybe I can make it a bit larger in...
width.
Maybe that will fix it?
Let's see if that...
Yeah. Okay, I'm not sure.
Anyway, let's just keep going.
Yeah.
Okay, I'm going to close you guys down. I'll see you on the other side again.
I think it should be fine, I hope.
Let's see here.
Wait, what is autofire?
Let's try autofire.
Wait, what is...
That's not already autofire?
Hold on.
Autofire off?
Huh?
Oh, is it with a bow maybe?
Wait.
Oh!
I see.
Okay, yeah, let's just keep it on, I guess.
I didn't realize that was the thing.
Okay, what was the plan? I was going west.
Because I'm going to fish.
Let me remove this real quick.
Wait, they're doing...
Rock, paper, scissor.
I saw that. I saw you, Dylan.
I saw you. Wait, hold on.
This breeze is really extra right now.
You wear flying needles, huh?
Well,
I don't give a happy end, bro.
Why would you say that even?
I was not expecting that from this game.
What the fuck?
Well, okay.
Alright, then.
You get to die, sir.
Wait, is that my torch?
Why does it look so different?
Oh, it's just a normal torch.
Never mind. It just looked differently colored.
In fact, I haven't really gone to the west very much.
So, this will be nice.
We have the adventure music.
Everything is going according to adventure plan.
Feels good, man.
Give me that.
Is this a special rock?
Hold on. Let me test something.
What is up here?
Can I go all the way up there?
I can do it.
Hold on.
What is... Hold on.
What is...
See, now I'm curious.
What the hell?
Let me get up there.
Okay.
Oh!
I hear enemies.
Get rid of all that.
Wait, are they up here?
Make a path.
Actually, activate this.
Oh, that's way better.
I guess there's nothing up here.
I'm still gonna go to the top because
why shouldn't I?
I wonder what happens
if you go really high up.
I can technically ascend
as much as I want, right?
You know what?
That's a great fucking idea. Let's try that.
I just want to see what happens.
Oh, this is gonna take a while, isn't it?
Is there a limit here?
Yeah, I don't know, man.
Nope!
Let's go down again.
I'm gonna try that later.
Maybe with another block.
I just want to see if there was anything up there.
Wait, is it me or does Abigail
do more damage now?
Four and five.
Usually you did like one damage.
Okay, now we're in hell again.
Wait!
Wait a minute.
What is...
What is that?
Is that an evil thingy?
You know what? Eat the...
Eat the shrimp, po-boy!
That works pretty well.
Man, I don't like the beeping.
It makes it sound like there's a bomb going off.
Gives me anxiety.
I died here, it seems.
I don't know where to delete that.
Nobody needs to know.
Nope, no, no, no.
Just circumvent all that.
I'm taking the vicious mushrooms.
Oh wait, I was here.
I haven't been this way though.
Look at these evil cacti.
I don't like that.
Oh shit, now we're in the desert again.
That's a pink prickly pear.
Used to make pink die.
Right.
Nothing.
Wait a minute, there's actually water there.
Oh wait, are we in the forest now? We're in the desert.
I actually forgot about that mission.
I'll do that later.
So the bunny here
comes with me.
This one is important.
Wait, debloom...
Seeds.
I can probably grow those myself, huh?
I just need to figure out how to do it properly.
That would mean infinite healing potions.
What's that?
Can of worms.
Cool.
Wand of sparking.
Grenades.
All these usual suspects here.
I shall take it.
Okay, let's head back out.
Stop that, will ya?
I shall now provide
all the sound effects in this game.
I'm kidding, that would be terrible.
Winter wonderland!
Oh, that's cool!
Look at that!
Ice slime.
Would it give me anything special?
38!
That's a nice amount of damage right there.
Oh, look at these frozen pots!
Cold water.
Oh, there's a pot!
Thank you.
What's this?
Oh, I'm sliding around!
Snow block.
I mean...
I'll take a bit of this.
Maybe I can do special things with it.
I shall take some of it.
Thank you.
I need...
Actually, I need to just bring whatever I can
to Dylan, you know?
Anything and everything.
I'm doing a bit, man.
This sword is fucking amazing.
It's a great sword.
What do we have down here?
That's a bit of a cave.
Ice torch!
Let's try the ice torch.
Very fitting.
Let me out of here.
My goodness.
Get me out of here.
I'm a bit too lazy to go around.
That's totally on me.
Give me this rope.
I like this sword a lot!
This is a nice sword.
Oh, it's getting dark.
Penguin!
Yeah!
It's a material.
That goes straight to Dylan.
Shiverthorn.
Shiverthorn seeds.
So I can grow them.
I like this music.
Winter Wonderland.
We ain't got shit down here.
Oh man, the damage of this sword is indeed great.
Uh oh, we're in hell again.
And it's the middle of the night.
That ain't good.
That ain't good, bruh.
Oliver has defeated the 50th crime mirror.
Oh man, the projectile here clears all this shit.
Along a line.
Oh, I love it.
This sword is frickin' fantastic.
What is that?
There's something in the thing here.
We got a heal.
We have amazing healing potions now.
This is a bit scary.
Oh god!
We got up, we got up.
Let's chillaxe for a moment.
Do we have our...
We don't have our thingy.
Heal again?
Okay, we're full health.
90...
Yo, this upgrade is...
bitchin'.
Holy shit.
Oh wait, it's only against the flying things, of course.
Man, the banners are...
something.
Pretty great.
Oh, shouldn't have taken that away so soon.
Man, take away some...
I don't know!
Water leaf.
Remove it.
Just keep going.
Fuck you.
Dude, this is...
You need to focus here.
What's that?
Face... oh, face monster banner.
What's the other banner?
Don't you fucking come near me.
Gonna have a little outpost here.
Look at that shit.
Is this also affecting...
Abigail?
Maybe it is, actually.
Look at that money.
Oh yeah.
Wait, is that an...
The banners do a...
lot to help here.
I could just hang out here for a bit and kill these.
Nah.
Let's keep moving.
Death wheat.
I want to get out of this fucking area.
Get me out of here!
You can't go on forever.
I think we're back.
Wait, do these have more HP?
82. No, that's not too bad.
Oh, what's that?
We've got a structure here.
Old man.
I hope you have like six friends standing around behind you.
I don't. Curse?
Oh! Oh!
What?
No.
No, no, no, no!
What's happening?
Oh, this is bad, isn't it?
Oh, I'm fucking...
Spine was ripped out?
Bro, the normal enemies are like,
ah, that's fucking easy.
Then you meet a boss, it's like, sit the fuck down.
I don't have a chance against
any of these fucking bosses.
What is going on?
That's a zombie.
No, I'm sorry!
I thought you were an enemy.
I apologize.
Quick stack that shit.
And let's...
Potions? You're not... let's...
Yeah, sure.
Ah, I should have used this. I didn't think in the moment.
Fuck!
Put...
This in there.
Ice torch?
Shiver's thorn.
Flux there.
No, this is construction, isn't it?
Goes in there.
And bombs?
Do good, do good, do good, do good.
Night owl?
Hmm. Sure.
Just eat one of them.
Okay, this looks better.
Penguin? You go in here.
I'm gonna keep these banners though.
Ah, wait a minute!
It took my Abigail.
Ah, you know what?
Use it and put it in here.
There's no reason to carry it around, I guess.
Okay, we gotta go back...
immediately.
Fucking old man turned into some kind of...
Okay.
Well, well, well.
It is time, but now I'm ready, bitch!
Now I'm ready!
Arms...
You know what? This is it!
This is it!
It's happening!
Give me...
the thingy.
That one. Let's try it.
Actually, I have an idea.
Let's actually lock that off.
They're coming from the west, right?
Uh, Catlin, get inside!
Come here! Get in!
Get in!
We're under attack!
Oh wait, I forgot about this.
Goblin Army has arrived!
Oh, they're right!
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
Fucking Catlin, I told you!
Kill them all.
Oh my god.
This is actually pretty effective, what I'm doing here.
Okay, they are kind of scary.
Fucking get inside!
They're inside the house!
Wait, I thought they were approaching from the west. What is this?
This looks like east to me.
Are you kidding me?
Oh god, they're inside the house.
Wow, Mortall just rinsed them.
Rain on them.
I need to heal in a second here.
Oh, no.
Mortall, come on!
Show me your skills.
Heal up.
Oh, we're taking damage here.
Oh, no.
The mages and the archers are fucking me up.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay.
Come on! There we go.
I need, uh...
Fuck, I can't do this right now.
Okay, we're doing well so far.
We're surviving.
The door is destroyed.
Block that shit.
Get away!
We gotta heal soon.
Okay, this is working wonders on the left.
And this rain right here is doing great.
The mages are the ones that
kinda fuck me up here.
They spawn inside the house.
Man, look at this. This is so effective.
Wait, that's it. Goblin Warrior Banner. Put it.
Oh, yeah.
Look at that.
That's way better.
Heal up.
This is going swimmingly.
Finally, I got some confidence here
in this game in combat.
I feel like I'm getting my ass kicked
normally, but...
not right now.
Oh, god.
Get rid of that guy.
Man, this right here is doing wonders!
Oh, wait, I just noticed!
There's a bar in the bottom right
that says cleared.
Holy shit.
I didn't even see that last time.
Wow.
Man, I kinda wanna...
Oh, god.
Can you please stop that?
Oh, my god, look at the damage.
Oh, shit!
Ye-ho!
Goblin Thief.
Thieves, huh?
Are we doing on the left side?
Everything's fine.
We've got an mage down here.
Gonna take care of him.
Look at this, man. I'm killing it.
I don't even need to do this.
This thing is so good.
Goblin Army has been defeated.
Heck, yeah, dude.
That was flawless performance right there.
Was there something over here?
What were you just fighting?
Oh, we can remove this now.
Man, this wall right here
did wonders.
I only had to focus on one side at a time.
That was great.
Now we put this back.
Look at that.
That's how we do it.
I'm proud of myself.
That was so nice.
I do wonder if I can...
upgrade this somehow or get a better one.
This banner right here
did a ton.
Let's put it over here with the rest.
Just organize them like that.
We even have this. I don't think we need that here though.
They're not gonna come here.
Okay.
That's great.
Organize.
Gob, wait.
Wait.
Oh, did I not just...
Okay, there we go.
I thought I just put it down.
What's that sound?
Why am I hearing...
What's that?
Oh, it's Abigail. Never mind.
God damn.
That was bad.
Why does it look like I'm some kind of cyborg?
Look at my arms.
Looks like I have like...
shotguns for arms
or for hands. Very interesting.
Okay, so
really quickly, let's repair this.
And use the wall.
There we go.
Beautiful.
So, that's done. Let me actually
remove these to make it a bit more aesthetic inside of here.
There we go.
Ah, that looks a bit better.
And then we only have the stone on the sides.
I kind of like that look.
And in the middle here, I guess.
Yeah, that's cool.
So, what I want to do now...
Let me quickly expand this house a little bit.
Also, where...
Yeah, we got to attract the gunman.
And apparently...
Pull on. Do we still have our gun?
We don't have any ammo, right?
No.
But the question is, do we need it
equipped or something?
I'm gonna try to have it equipped.
I need wood.
And a lot of it.
And wall.
Maybe I'll make planked wall.
How about that?
Actually, I need windows too.
Glass wall.
We're gonna build a little higher up over here.
Maybe it's getting a bit too much.
I don't know, but...
I want...
Oh, you know what, actually?
I can make much smaller rooms.
I don't need these rooms to be this big.
Just occurred to me.
It doesn't have to be that crazy.
What if we make...
Marathon medalist.
What?
Traveler to...
What? That's a very specific amount of miles.
What's the deal with 26.2?
I don't get that.
We're gonna make like, pots here.
Not very glamorous.
But whatever.
What is this?
Wait a minute.
One, two, three, four, five.
This is six, isn't it?
One, two, three. It is.
Okay.
So we need it there.
Let's circle this place.
Yeah, this room gets to be bigger.
What? This is not a room.
This is gonna be the...
Ooh, that's actually...
That's how we do it!
We're gonna have like,
the stairwell
in the center there.
And then rooms on either side.
I like that.
I do indeed like that.
Let's make doors.
We need...
Lots of them.
There, there.
Oh, but wait a minute. This is gonna be awkward.
They have to walk through
each other to...
I mean, that's the consequence of living in a 2D world, bitch!
I can't do anything about that. That's just how the game is.
That's how the game is.
Too fucking bad!
I'm gonna need some more wall.
Oh, what is the other wall I can make?
And how do I do that?
Wait, Dylan?
Plank wall?
Needs stone block.
I have a shit ton of that.
Let's make some plank wall here.
Let's just vary it a little bit, huh?
Oh, I can just make a pure stone also,
but that's not what I want.
Do I need this first, I think? Hold on.
Wait, what?
Do I need it over here?
Ah!
That requires...
Perfect.
Let's make a bunch of that.
Let's just try this out.
You know what? This would look nice
in a storage area.
Like a little storage room?
Oh, you know what? Actually,
we do that. We put this
in the storage room. This looks like
some kind of storage...
situation, doesn't it?
Oh, that looks so good!
Oh, yeah!
Or maybe even a basement.
I'm just gonna vary this a little bit.
It's gonna be a little random.
That's okay.
Okay.
Everything is an experiment.
And we're gonna need some goddamn
chairs.
One, two, three.
And some tables.
Let's do...
No!
Hup, hup, hup, hup.
Uh, hold on.
Oh,
shiisa!
No!
It's time to get my ass kicked again.
There's...
Like, what can I do, you know?
Uh, Abigail is here.
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
Defense?
Running speed!
No, uh, didn't I have a running speed potion?
Sword!
Shit. Huh?
Didn't I have a running speed potion?
I'm pretty sure it...
God damn diddly did!
Dah!
Okay, we're gonna die.
That's okay. We have 31 defense though.
Isn't that kind of nice?
Okay, here we go.
Let me try the sword, I guess.
No, actually, this is better.
If I miss, it's really gonna fuck me.
It's shooting the little fucking thingies.
It's really annoying.
Also, I should be close to my house here
so I can heal.
Oh, what's happening?
Get him!
Oh, he's doing that shit now.
Wait, I'm actually...
Oh, God!
Stand in the fucking rain!
Ah!
That thing fucks me.
DPS!
Come on! Stand in the rain!
No!
Man!
That was so close!
Fuck!
Okay, man. Definitely...
It's all about buffing yourself here.
Definitely.
Okay.
Well, it's getting better and better
every time.
One day I'll get it.
One day.
I'm gonna put a door here as well.
I'm just gonna continue what I was doing.
Let's have a little light in here as well.
There.
Very nice.
Okay.
Man, I just need to make a bunch of tables.
Maybe I'll make one of these.
Wait, didn't I have a shit ton of those?
What am I gonna table that?
Oh, I already... ah, okay. It's fine.
Everything is fine.
Table right there.
Then we're gonna have a table right here.
With a nice chair.
Chair there.
The table like that.
That's why not.
Let's see here.
Glass.
Nice little window there.
Let's make it like...
That looks pretty neat.
Look at that!
That looks nice.
Doesn't it?
Get out of that chair.
It's right over there.
And then we're gonna need some...
Some of this.
Doors.
Ah, I need more doors.
I need all the doors.
Okay, let's see here.
Is this gonna be annoying?
That's gonna be annoying, isn't it?
You're gonna...
That's okay. This can be a room.
That's okay. Let's just do that.
That's fine.
The right side is part of this.
It's gonna be a little annoying for the people there, but that's okay.
Man!
I did not make enough chairs.
This should be fine, I think.
Man, there's so many stars.
Where'd you come from?
Bastard.
Let's see here.
Man, we have so many people!
Still in so many.
I need a chair.
I mean, now I made room for...
fucking the next million people coming here.
There. Let's see here.
Is this enough?
This...
No!
Oh, okay.
It's too small.
Well...
Let me test something.
Will vertical work?
That's suitable!
Amazing.
That's a little weird room there, but that's okay.
A little bit of asymmetry is always good, isn't it?
That's what I always say.
Okay.
Uh...
Cremera. Yeah, sure. Let's hang it.
Hang all the banners here.
Actually, that doesn't look too bad!
I kind of like how that looks.
Right above the furnace.
Pretty cool.
Spiky ball!
Let's try it on this squirrel.
Oh!
It roll! Oh!
That's cool!
Let me try and equip this now.
Hold on. What did Dylan say?
Let me see if I can make him say it again.
Dylan.
Not all of the undead monsters are hostile.
I hear one even sells merchandise deep on the ground.
Really?
Clearly.
Well, well, well.
If you thought rainy days were a drag,
wait till you see it raining slime.
I've seen it.
If you place an empty bottle on a table,
you can use it to craft all sorts of neat potions.
Thank you! You could have told me that earlier.
Hang up any banners you earn from defeating foes
as they will help you in future combat with that creature.
Yes.
It's pretty cold in the snow biome,
but there are some unique treasures there as well.
Well, I'd check it out.
You actually call it a biome?
I don't know, man. I feel like that's a bit weird.
There are ant-lion tunnels deep beneath the desert,
full of rare fossils and many hazards.
I know.
If you find a marble biome, be careful.
They say that these locations are inhabited
by some very dangerous creatures.
I believe you.
In granite biomes, the very stone itself is a threat,
frequently coming to life.
Bro.
Okay.
If you ever need a break from all this adventuring,
there's always time for some good old fashioned fishing.
You know what?
Speaking of fishing,
thanks for reminding me, Dylan.
I need to go fish.
Put that in there.
All these three.
I'm going to go fish.
I'll be back later.
Wait a minute.
Did I ever find...
Actually, hold on. There's water down there. Will that work?
Let me actually test.
I want to see if I can fish in the cave.
I see there's water down here.
What?
It's kind of crazy that there's like
a little house down here,
right beneath where I started.
Okay, there's water here.
Let's see.
Oh, it's working.
Base!
Here we go.
Come on.
But I thought that was the bonny fish
for a second.
Wouldn't create.
Apprentice bait.
Dante!
The arm stealer has arrived.
Bro.
Bro!
I'll be coming right to you.
Hold your phone.
And there it fucking is.
Let's see what you got.
What do you got?
Dante.
Is that you?
Dante?
No, that's the...
Dante. There you are.
Hey, this ain't a movie, pal.
Ammo is extra.
Happiness.
Hey, I can't do what I do with so many people watching me.
Think Catlin the nurse ever, you know,
checks me out?
I don't really like lion pines,
the golfer being on my turf, you know.
I'd really like to use mortal
the demolitionist as a range target.
Some...
What?
Okay, so you just arrived,
but you were already hot for Catlin.
And you're
hating...
on mortal.
That's cool.
Musketball!
Tell me it didn't automatically.
Okay, it didn't.
Thank God, I thought it automatically used all that,
but it only used what I had in my inventory.
Bro, I'm set for life.
Lovely. I love it.
And now, check this out. Dylan.
Plop!
What can you make me?
Meteor shots.
Silver...
Tongs? Oh, nine. Oh, yeah, baby.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah! 12?
Cursed flame.
Okay, I don't know.
Man, it smells great. Someone is making food.
And I like the smell of it.
It's annoying me.
Um...
Endless...
musket pouch.
Whoops.
That's okay.
It's okay because... listen.
Listen.
Hold on. Hold on now.
I'll show you why it's okay.
Dylan?
Tell me about this again.
Uh...
Okay, I don't know how to make that.
So, what's this?
There's money on the ground.
What the fuck?
Hold on. Dylan?
Nope.
Uh, yeah. Hold on.
Dylan.
I need to see this again.
Tongsten.
Tongsten bar.
Requires anvil.
Oh, yeah. I'm gonna make Tongsten shit.
Look how many I have.
Oh, here we go.
Very weak knockback.
Weak knockback.
Oh, mama.
Let's just make one.
Because I want to see something.
Dylan.
What about this?
Wait, what?
Oh, I thought it was a material. Never mind.
Alright, that confirms it.
We're gonna make a shit ton of this.
Not too much, though.
Let's see here.
There.
2450 is the perfect amount.
Yeah, buddy.
Oh, right.
Coins is for this.
I thought this Coins ammo was like...
The name of Ion Yu.
Defeat the Eye of Ketulu.
An ocular menace who only appears at night.
Hold on.
Speaking of ocular menaces.
Let me check them out here.
Can I?
Demon Eye?
They only appear in nighttime.
Can I not see the big guy?
Wait, unlocks?
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
Can I search?
What was it called?
Ock?
No, wait.
Ketulu or something.
Eye.
Demon Eye.
Wait.
Maybe I need to defeat it to get a beast theory of it, actually.
That's probably what that means.
Wait, desert?
The arms dealer has everything.
Anyone could need to shoot things dead.
From little round bullets to guns made from sh...
Speaking of guns made from sharks.
Dylan, uh, I mean Dante.
I see your eyeball in the mini shark.
How'd you know?
You really don't want to know how it was made.
Let me guess.
A shark?
44 gold?
But it's like terrible.
No, wait, it has insanely fast speed.
I mean...
I obviously got a flintlock pistol though.
13?
I wish it would show me DPS.
But I mean, I'm going to try all these of course.
I want to save for the mini shark.
Because that looks like a goddamn
minigun, doesn't it?
And that sounds straight up my name.
My alley.
So yeah.
Quick the undertaker.
Bro, I can finally shoot my gun!
Pew, pew, pew, pew!
Oh my god.
Calm down.
It's happening.
Let's organize inventory.
And let's...
We've got to go down again first.
We need to fish.
We need to...
fish.
So we have a quest.
There's a brat
that has requested our services.
And who are we to deny this brat?
We do need our daily brat.
There we go.
And we fish.
Look at how the water sort of disconnects here.
That's interesting.
Oh, we're using the good bait here as well.
Look at this.
Wait a minute.
Didn't we get a potion that would
increase chance of finding
boxes?
Not defense.
No, maybe...
Am I fucking imagining things?
Or maybe I saw it in
when talking to Dylan.
That's probably what that was.
Base.
What's that down there?
Hold on, what's that?
Are you fucking kidding me?
No way.
What the fuck?
That was there all the time?
Jesus!
Ow!
Oh, we gotta shoot this motherfucker!
Pew, pew!
Come here.
I'm so heavy I can't use my gun!
Fuck you!
Oh, I love it.
There's more.
Come at me, bro.
There we go.
Oh, I got a crate.
Lead bar, cool.
I would love to see some weed right now.
Water throw!
Threading the needle!
Old shoe, been a while.
Kind of cool that I can fish down here, actually.
So I think it's just about the size
of the volume of water.
Because there is a small, I guess,
puddle upstairs that
doesn't do shit.
Specular fish?
Well, well, well, Dylan.
I have something to show you later.
Over a cup of tea.
Just you wait, sir.
Princess bait.
There's a slime there.
I kind of want to go explore this cave some more.
Because it's right beneath my house,
which is kind of cool.
Man.
Hmm.
Where is this bunny fish?
I'm getting lots of specular fish.
Oh my god.
Thank you.
Gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
Gimme!
Nah!
Okay, you know what?
Maybe I can't get it in a cave.
I'm gonna experiment some other place.
Dude, I have a sick melee weapon now
and a sick ranged weapon.
It's so sick it makes me vomit.
But the good kind of vomit.
Way!
Okay.
Real quick, Dylan needs to see this.
Why is Dylan in here?
Oh, it's a multiplayer thing.
That's how I make them.
Well, I have a lot of them, so whatever.
Unless...
Wait a minute.
I'm gonna test something real quick.
Bottle to water and blink root.
I have blink...
...somewhere.
There, no wait, this is seeds.
Blink root.
And then water bottles.
We need water for that?
In fact, wait a minute.
Is that water?
Oh, we need a water bottle, of course.
We also have
bucket of water there.
Potions.
Hold on a sec.
What was I doing?
Glass.
I need glass.
That's glass. Oh, no, I made it all into it, didn't I?
I wonder if this will work
if I make it into glass. Hardened sand?
Hey!
Any sand block!
Awesome!
Delete that.
And then we're gonna make some bottles.
I don't need to do this anyway.
And then...
we'll go find a water source.
Wait, wait, wait.
Is that not enough?
Maybe I need to be...
in a larger volume of water?
Let's try this.
Let's make like 50 of these.
Awesome.
It's a whole process here.
Make this potion, huh?
Okay.
I want to see if this works on NPCs.
That was my whole plan.
Wait, what is this?
Teleport you to a party member.
Click their head on the full screen map.
Nah.
I don't think it works...
with NPCs.
Unfortunately...
Whoops.
This gun is incredible.
Rrrrr!
Oh my god.
Look at it taking cover.
You deserve to live.
Delete that.
What is this even for?
Wait, I can use this to make this as well.
Okay.
It's time to go exploring.
This is stuff like this right here.
I'm going to put it in here.
It's trash, right?
Makes total sense to me.
Oh, this is actually full.
This is the second one.
Let's call this...
Organics 2.
Or just organics, I guess.
They're both organics.
Yep, yep, yep.
Apprentice bait.
We're all going to keep that.
The cell is harpoon.
I think we're going to keep that as well.
This one is very good.
I'm going to save this until the...
eye comes back.
Then I'm going to fuck it up with my new gun.
Just drink this.
This one.
I'm going to go east now and cross the ocean.
And that's what I'm going to do.
Actually, I can make some quick potions here.
I need this and...
this.
And what else?
Why is this so hard to remember?
It's insane.
Gel, right.
The gel, the good old yellow.
It requires two of them and glowing.
That's a whole process, dude.
That's fine.
Let's go.
Summon that.
Grab these.
Yikes.
And there we go. And then we leave.
There we go.
See ya, people. See ya later.
I'm going east.
Let's see if I can't find a little...
...body of water. Actually...
Wow!
You get to see... Wow, this is...
Oh. That's a great map.
Oh, the gun is great!
I love the gun!
I have enough ammo as well.
Look, 9, 5, 2.
I do wonder if it's using the good or shit ammo first.
Let's try to remove this.
So I did like 24.
So 24, 19.
Actually, I'm not sure.
Oh, let's see. 7, 4, 7, 4.
Okay, it's using the shitty ones first.
But... Ah!
Now it's using the good ones. Okay, gotcha.
So that's how that works.
Oh, the gun is fantastic!
I love shooting things.
Okay, just cross this really quickly.
Give me vicious mushrooms.
Okay, it's a little bit difficult to aim with this thing.
I just need to practice a bit, I think.
Whoa, that was a funny little way of traversing there.
Look at all this fucking growth.
Whoa!
Deathweed is mine.
I feel a little too...
comfortable right now or...
confident, I think.
I need to tone it down.
That's empty.
Look at me, just plinking everyone.
This game is easy! No, it's not.
It's actually not. But it's easy!
Keep going, we're soon there.
Get across there.
Actually, I want to try and fish here.
For a second.
Wait, we're using something orange?
Oh, the apprentice bait.
There's an air balloon in the back!
Who's that?
Come on, quick!
Alright, shoot him down.
Shoot him down!
Fuck off. I'm fishing.
Yeah!
A menacing radar.
Is that better than what I have?
Hmm.
I'm not sure.
4%?
I feel like I take more damage than I deal.
Do I, though?
240?
Willy!
Fuck this spider.
Fuck everything. We're leaving.
I'm gonna make a little fast way through here.
Minecraft style.
Just for future.
Man, I want to make a railway
through this entire region.
From left to right.
That's what I want to make.
I think it's a great idea.
What is this area now?
This has to be a jungle, no?
Look at the background.
It's like the Amazon rainforest.
Rainforest.
I just want to take a quick look down here, actually.
What's that?
Oh, there's nothing special down here.
There we go. I got up.
I want to get to the ocean.
Shoot him down.
Man, I can't grab the trees.
But there was one thing that allowed me to grab the trees.
I remember reading that.
Moon glow.
Oh!
I saw that in a recipe.
For something.
And it was exciting.
Look at this clear water.
Grubby!
Okay.
What's up, bitch?
That's my torch.
Man, did I really go this far?
Damn!
I have no memory of going this far.
I guess I did.
It was very far away.
What the hell is that in there?
Why is there such a weird looking...
block in there?
It's just dirt!
Huh.
Oh yeah, I made this. I remember this now, huh?
Oh!
Mushrooms be good.
The world here is bigger than you think.
Damn.
I thought I was so close to the ocean.
And yet I feel like I'm...
Where am I?
I'm soon there, but wow!
Wow!
Man, the double jump.
Imagine if I didn't find that.
This is so much better.
Here we go.
This is the cozy spot.
Look at this. Isn't that cool?
Let's just remove some blocks while we're here
and we're chilling a bit.
So here we go.
Oh!
Yeah, dude!
Where are we going?
What?
No way!
You're kidding.
That's the end?
Oh wait, does that mean that's the end of the world?
On the right side?
No way.
I need to see what's down here.
This is going to be my death, isn't it?
Do I not have a...
Shit, I don't.
I need a water breathing potion.
Oh god.
All right!
Hey!
Here's a quick question though.
What if I were to...
Look at this shit.
That's how you do it.
Oh, I'm actually going to die though.
We got to get back up. It's not good enough.
We need a potion for this.
Yeah, this is not working.
Okay.
Well...
Hmm.
You know what?
Maybe I will...
Let me just remove some of this.
Let me move the gel.
Sand blocks.
Dayblooms.
I really need to figure out how to
plant these fucking things properly.
I'm going to go back.
Yeah.
Okay, I have good stuff.
Quickly check out the chests.
Let's also remove this right here.
It's unfitting.
I was about to say.
I feel like I crafted more before and I couldn't see them,
but I just accepted it.
Okay, well...
Now I need
these ones.
Make them all
beautiful.
And I'm going to go west again.
Because that seems like the place to go
with the old man and all that.
Let's see.
Slowly regenerates life.
This one is nice.
See, plus one defense.
I feel like maybe this is better.
Maybe the damage output is really the thing.
I mean, if you kill them fast enough,
they're not going to do damage to you, right?
That's my thinking there.
Actually, just use this button.
And then we have some stuff like that.
Put them in there.
What potions did I have here?
Invisibility.
Really quickly.
Dylan, could you tell me about
water breathing?
Water breathing.
Huh.
Maybe you can't tell me about that.
This needs pink gel.
Let's put tools and stuff in here.
This is like the tool thingy.
Bombs.
Take the bombs.
Yeah, take the bombs.
Yeah, I used this actually.
The sickle.
I didn't try that yet.
Let's try that.
Let's see how that works.
Aha!
Give me all the hay.
That's another way to remove grass, I guess.
Not with the lawn mower.
Give me all of it.
This way we also prevent spawning of enemies.
You can totally do some
speed increases with this if you do it right.
Oh yeah, baby.
Okay!
Put it back in the toolbox.
And let's see what we can do with the hay, huh?
Nope, no, no, no.
It goes in here.
No, ah!
Moon glow gelge.
Wait, what?
Organics.
And you go... ah, there's no room.
So you go in here instead.
A bait goes in there.
Not actually...
I don't know.
Do I even really want this anymore?
Hmm.
I mean, yeah, I do.
I do.
Dylan, what about the hay?
Target dummy.
And hay wool.
You know what? Let's make a target dummy.
Ah, that needed wood, I believe.
Here it is.
Oh, that's actually...
Oh, nice.
See, this is nice.
Hold on.
Plus 4%. Let's see here.
25, 23, 21.
That's not going to change much.
That's nice to have.
We can test some damage with different weapons.
That ain't bad.
I do like that.
Construction...
Hay goes in here.
Worm put in there.
And let's rock and roll!
Let's go!
Willy!
Okay, fine.
I'm staying home.
No, you departed.
Fine.
Let me put my money up here, actually, before I leave.
There we go. Now we have nothing to lose, literally.
Oh, no!
Okay, I guess I'll stay.
Hold on.
Uh...
Fuck.
Prepare...
Uh...
Fuck, what do we have?
Arrow speed?
Can I...
Okay, I definitely need this.
This one.
33 armor right now.
Hold on. Do we have a banner for eye?
Blood crawler?
Blue slime?
Zombie?
I don't know. Okay, okay, we gotta get ready.
Let's fight out here again.
Next to this. We need to do this.
This was the strategy.
Equip this.
I'm gonna be shooting, and I'm gonna be harpooning.
I'm gonna be sorting.
It's gonna be great.
Maybe even here.
Oh, what's happening?
Oh, okay. Here we go.
Here we go.
Fuck you!
Change direction.
Okay, so far so good.
Man, the gun is great. The gun is great.
I'm liking the gun.
Shoot the little ass.
Oh, he's going mad now.
Oh, god.
Get him!
Oh, shit. Here we go.
Nice. We're doing great.
This is the strategy.
Get him. Change direction.
Yep. Go, go, go.
Shoot him down.
Come on.
Heal up.
The other way, the other way.
There's a fucking zombie over there kicking my ass.
That's it!
Fucking third times the charm.
Or was it fourth? I don't remember.
A treasure bag!
Shield of Cthulhu!
Crimson...
Crim-tane ore!
That's a lot of it, too!
Wait.
33...
Wait, it...
Oh, wait a minute.
Equippable.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
How does this work?
It allows the player to dash into the enemy, double-tap it.
That's gonna do damage?
Am I not gonna take damage from dashing through, I wonder?
Oh my god, bro!
That's awesome!
Yo-ho!
That's freaking great!
I love that.
Okay, man. That was fucking awesome!
Okay, that needs to be celebrated.
Dylan!
Look what I got!
Oh, am I just killing things I walk into from now on?
That seems a little...
excessive.
Crim-tane.
We be smelting.
Gimme.
Let's see what we can make.
What can we make?
Blood... oof. Tendenbow!
Flesh... oh! Fleshcatcher.
Hmm.
This one, though.
Artery?
What?
12?
Hold on, now.
10. I could make both if I wanted.
Oh, man.
20 range of damage, bro.
No! I'm gonna be shooting. I'm not gonna be bowing anything.
I like my gun.
Dude, what is this? I need to try this.
I also need to try this.
It's a material. Hold on.
Blade of... okay. Huh.
Interesting.
Let me try these out.
Wait. Oh!
Oh!
What? That's awesome!
It's a yo-yo!
I guess sort of...
Bro, that's...
That's awesome!
Oh, this looks badass, though.
Look at this! With the shield and the...
Oh, yeah, baby!
Oh, I'm going straight...
Somewhere right now to kill things.
Oh, mama.
Uh...
Get rid of that.
What's happening? Ah, here we go.
Yo, that's pretty neat, too.
Oh.
This weapon, though.
That's kind of nuts.
Yo, that's crazy!
Get...
Get rammed into.
Oh, my God, I'm unstoppable!
Old man, here I come!
Where you at, old man?
I will fuck you up!
Oh, yeah.
It was a night and...
It was a dark and stormy night.
And Oliver had acquired the evilest of gear.
Ready to face any...
Any challenge?
Just go... Are we way faster as well?
I'm not sure here what's happening.
Bro, I kill everything with ease.
It's not even a problem.
Fuck off!
Ah, okay, yeah, so there's...
There's actually only a max range here.
So that's like the drawback of this one.
Dude, I can't be stopped.
This is unreal.
Come on.
Alright, let's shoot some bitches.
Let's chop some bitches!
Does that make him bleed?
Hold on.
Wait, I'm liking the yoyo better here, I think.
The yoyo is actually...
The artery here is...
It's quite something, isn't it?
Bro, why am I so slow suddenly?
Mighty wind!
Whoa!
What's this?
Angry...
Tumbler.
Oh, it's very easy to accidentally...
Charge with that thing.
Kind of confusing.
Oh, I'm kicking ass. I can't be stopped in this game.
This is insanity.
Insanity!
Fuck you, slime!
You can't kill me?
Oh, nice. Look at this.
We're shielded from the wind in here.
Fuck off, bunny.
Dude, this is amazing.
Finally, I killed the Eye of Catoilo.
I have become the master of this world.
Nothing shall ever stop me.
Mushrooms for me, mushrooms for you.
We're having lots of fun.
And we're only a few.
How do I... Right, there we go.
Rosalva the Dryad has arrived.
I remember, uh...
Was it Joe telling me about the Dryad?
See, that's exciting.
Exciting.
Ooh, it's getting...
Ooh, it's windy and cold.
Uh-oh.
Get away, fish.
Let me yo-yo you.
This is such a weird weapon.
But it's really fun.
It's a great weapon.
However, shooting though is...
Fantastic as well, isn't it?
Honestly, why am I so slow?
Ooh, chilled. I'm chilled.
I am chilled, man.
I'm chilling hard today.
Dude, this Friday has been great.
And it's not over yet.
Uh...
Yeah, just go.
Eh, eh, eh.
Look. He's bleeding.
Yep. It applies a bleed effect.
Let's do some gardening.
Kind of reminds me a little bit of those, uh...
What do you call it? The grass trimmers?
You know the ones that have this spinny thing?
A little plastic piece that spins.
What the fuck?
No! Don't, don't torch it.
Wait, uh...
I'm trying to get used to holding shift and doing this.
Why is this the...
I wonder if I can charge through this and not take damage.
I don't think I can.
Oh, but I can make sick jumps like that. Look!
Oh, yeah!
Boah! Boah, boah, boah, boah!
Feels amazing, yo.
Okay, old man, I'm coming for you, ass.
It's time to die, bitch.
Because I've got the weapons.
And I've got the shield.
It's time for you to take a nose dive!
If you know what I mean. Is he still here, though?
He's here.
What if I just shoot him immediately?
My master cannot be summoned under the light of day.
Okay, guess I'll wait till night.
Yoink! I want this.
Bah! I need to have the pig eggs on my three.
I cannot do the shift thing. It sucks.
Is there a duck in here?
We've got this!
Knowledge!
Molten Legion.
Diabolic?
Carriage Lantern.
What's that?
Calming Potion.
Increases enemy spawn rate.
Oh!
It contains strange symbols.
Yeah, okay.
Metal Shelf.
Give me that.
I'm getting a lot of banners here.
Actually, I'm running out of space.
I kind of want to delve into this place.
Should I, though?
I kind of want to teach this guy a lesson.
You know what? It's going to be a little difficult because...
I think the thing that really helped me before
was that I had a lot of space to run on.
So I'm actually going to quickly prepare a little bit here.
Hold on.
Get rid of that tree.
I'm going to make sort of a semi-flat ground here.
I think it's going to help.
There we go.
I guess I could just make it super flat.
Oh, fuck. Get off of me!
Can't you see I'm doing things, sir?
You got to take the trees from the bottom.
I'm going to remove this.
Actually, it's nice that while I'm chopping down the tree,
the movement of the axe also damages enemies.
You know, it's a little nice detail there.
Give me all that.
Something like this.
Because if I'm about to fight this guy,
I can't be getting stuck on terrain and shit.
Oh, there's a chest here.
Ooh.
It's an aura of light.
Just drink it.
Shit. I don't know.
I'll put this in here.
Hold on. Is it better to have it behind them?
What can I throw away? This one?
Tattered cloth? Hmm.
Oh, yeah. If you have the yo-yo behind them,
it sort of bounces behind them really quickly.
That's more damage.
I guess this is fine.
Is it night yet?
No, I don't think it is.
I cannot let you enter it.
Oh, yeah. Watch me.
Watch me enter.
Man, my inventory is full.
Green brick? Fuck that.
What can I get rid of?
Daybloom?
Maybe the Vicious Mushroom. I don't want that.
All the metal shells? Whatever.
Yeah. What's that?
A skull.
Okay.
Ooh.
Now, this is a real dungeon.
Golden key.
Opens one locked gold chest or lockbox.
Grenades? Fuck your dungeon!
Let's get rid of them.
Bone welder!
Hell, yeah!
Wood? Bottles? Night?
Just drink that.
Cool.
Hopefully I killed something down here.
Oh, wait. There's no more.
Huh.
Maybe I need to do some digging.
Oh, God.
Just use this.
Get up there.
Okay, we're definitely deying now.
Come back.
What do you mean? I already entered.
Unless he opens like a magic little area.
Let me try and dig.
Oh, this is annoying. This is going to take ages.
So, okay.
I'm gonna...
What am I gonna do?
I'm gonna go around it for now.
Until it's night.
I want to come back and kick that guy's ass.
Ooh, what is...
Sunflower.
You know what?
That looks pretty nice. I kind of just want to decorate.
I kind of want to make a little garden and figure out the whole...
Uh-oh.
I want to figure out the whole...
Oh, shit!
Get up there.
The farming.
Okay.
That works.
What's this?
Yellow marigold.
Um...
You know what? Let me try and fish here a bit.
Oh, we probably don't have any...
space in our inventory.
Sorry.
I need to remove some stuff.
Why did I bring this?
It's so dumb of me.
What should I remove?
Maybe this.
Let's see what happens here.
Oh, wait. I don't have any bait.
Wait. Do I know?
Hold on a sec.
Hey!
I do have bait.
I got a little ladybug.
Base.
Oh, here comes the slime invasion.
Uh, Abigail, do you want to take that?
No? Okay.
Yeah, the sword is my least favorite, I think.
It just... though attack rate,
not that much damage, low range.
You know? It's not optimal.
I don't...
Oh, did I just? Yeah, I just lost the bait.
Shit.
Abigail, take care of that slime!
Actually, it's about to be night.
It's about to be night.
Ooh, we actually have a lot of gold on us.
If we die.
Hmm.
And you know what?
A trader just appeared.
Oh wait, will it not catch anything without bait?
Is it like you catch nothing?
That's probably the case here.
Give me that.
I mean, I am tempted to catch...
Whoa!
Uh, this one.
Here's the thing.
My inventory is full.
And I need to put my gold in a chest.
So I'm gonna go back.
Where's my thing?
And then I'm gonna come back for the old man.
Hopefully when... oh, also look at this.
And celebration of me defeating the eye?
Is that what's happening?
Molten Legion.
So here's the thing.
The old man was a skeleton.
I wonder if any of these classified marching bones...
See, that could be...
That could mean skeletons.
I kind of just want to place a bunch of banners over there when I fight them.
Just to cover all my bases.
Um...
Wait, did I get a thingy?
Wait a minute.
Menacing... oh, you're right.
How good is this really?
Banner of generation. That's like the question.
Quick climbing clause.
Wait, I never tried this.
But I guess the 4% movement speed isn't bad.
Can I make... can I make...
Can I make better armor?
Because that's like the big thing here.
Can I make platinum armor?
Can I somehow upgrade this?
Now, tungsten already have, right?
Maybe you need to make diamond armor or something.
Also, I never tried the ice.
With the dude.
Snow. Dylan!
Check this out, my dude.
What a beautiful night.
With your recent victory, the world seems more at peace.
And these lanterns are in celebration of that.
Thank you, Dylan.
That is so nice of you. Help me.
While you explore the underground, you may occasionally encounter helpful fairies.
If you follow them, maybe they will lead you to treasure.
Crimson hearts can usually be found in the chasms around crimson areas.
I'm guessing that's the whole...
fucked up place with all the face enemies.
Smashing too many will unleash the brain of Katulhu.
The feeding this foe may cause meteors to fall out of the sky.
Meteorite?
And that's what happened.
That's how I did that last time.
Gotcha.
You will want to increase your life before facing your next challenge.
15 hearts should be enough.
Wow, that's very specific.
I have 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 10, 12.
Oh, so you want me to have 300 HP.
When the moon goes red, the water becomes like blood.
Creatures submerged within may become grotesque and malicious.
Really?
That's interesting.
You can even remove people from their home from the housing interface.
Right-click the banner hanging in their house.
You can also left-click to assign them a new home.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Stylist.
A lot of people have moved in lately, haven't they?
If it gets much more busy around here, a party girl will surely move in?
Is it just me or is this... weird?
What the fuck does that mean?
If Seymour's wares don't interest you, a wandering merchant often visits with exotic merchandise you might prefer.
Speak enough.
Is he here?
Wait, we're Selva?
Oh, wait a minute!
Dry it!
Have you tried using purification powder on the crimstone of the crimson?
I have not.
What is that?
Oh, you mean like the red stuff?
I have not. Happiness.
Is this area becoming rather dense or is it just me?
I was disliked the feeling.
I dislike the feeling. I don't like that Izzy the Angler has no respect for other beings.
I hate lion pines, the gulfers, destructive habits towards nature.
Oh, you mean like erecting golf courses?
I can see that.
You're like an elf, I guess.
What's your status?
The robust can is 6% crimson.
You have a lot of work to do?
My world is 6% crimson.
Does that mean this will... hold on a second.
Purification powder.
Aha!
Wait, really?
I'm gonna try that.
Guide to environmental preservation.
Prevent you from accidentally destroying the environment while in the inventory.
Oh.
Magically moves dirt.
It's too expensive. I want to try it though.
Blink root planter box!
Yeah, we gon' try that.
In fact, I have an idea.
This is a great idea.
Hold your horses.
Flowers, ooh.
All kinds of seeds, huh?
That's cool.
Well, I have an idea.
And for that, I need wood.
Yoink.
Also, click this button.
Wow, nothing? Okay.
Let's have a...
We should almost have a banner chest.
Let's just throw this in here for now.
Oh, that's a carriage lantern.
Let me hang that somewhere.
Or put it somewhere.
Who would like this carriage lantern?
Maybe it fits here.
Or, you know what?
Yeah!
That looks great and it fits a gunman, doesn't it?
That's cool.
Bone welder!
That's some dark shit right there.
Aw, really? Why does that not...
I thought this was background.
Boo!
Put it there.
Oh, that's looking nasty.
Wait.
Huh?
Oh, that blocked the door.
Interesting.
Oh, that's a small one.
I thought that was bigger.
Okay, well, we can put it there, I guess.
I guess I need to buy more of them, huh?
We need to have like a greenhouse.
Multiple layers.
I just planned all kinds of shit.
You know?
What's this? Antlion?
Oh my god, all the banners.
The bone welder.
Let me remove this. Put it somewhere else.
There.
Let me remove this.
Put it, I don't know, like there.
And then we can have this ugly-ass thing.
That does something.
Let's see.
Snow brick.
Ice brick. Snow bowl.
Interesting.
Now, you.
Tell me about snow.
Snowfall block.
Wait.
Is that ammo?
No way.
Oh my god, have I been able to do this all this time?
Oh well.
You learn. You live, you learn.
Ice blocks? What can we do?
I knew it was going to be something like this, by the way.
I freaking knew it.
Thin ice.
We can make a...
a frozen hotel somewhere.
An ice hotel.
Living frostfire block.
Interesting.
Let's throw that stuff in there.
Topaz.
The book.
Sunflowers. You know what? Let me plant the sunflowers.
Let's put them out here in the garden.
That looks nice.
It's starting to look like a home.
Tattered cloth? Hey, Dylan!
My man. What can I do with this?
A goblin?
Why shouldn't I make that?
Nah. Nah.
Don't want to make it.
The golden key opens one locked golden key.
I'm intrigued by that.
This one is weird.
Put it in here.
Oh, yeah. Put this in here as well.
Here's what I'm going to do, though.
I need wood again.
I'm going to bring a campfire with me
to the old man.
I need all the buffs I can get, right?
Actually, before I go there,
I kind of want to go back into the...
into the crimson
and see if I can't
defeat that brain there.
Tattered cloth.
Put it here.
Put it there.
Oh, yeah. I also want to try this purification powder.
What else should I bring, though?
On my journey.
Zombie?
I guess I can bring these.
Spiky bowl.
I actually want to bring these. These seem pretty interesting.
And the grenades?
Wait, this...
Was there a difference there?
I don't know what I'm trying to say.
Let me see here.
Nice torch.
Flare.
I'm going to be on my way.
Actually,
cremera...what's this?
Demon eye.
I'm going to bring these two with me.
Going down there.
I want to, you know,
do things.
Alright.
You get sort of slowed down.
Can you do this?
I deposited my money.
Great.
What is this again?
I want to plant everything, actually.
Bro, this yo-yo is actually a real gardening tool.
Look at this. I can remove all the grass like this.
Who needs a lawnmower?
This is even faster!
The lawnmower sucks. What's that?
It's just lead.
Was it here?
Wait a minute.
What did I find down there?
We've got red stuff here.
And here, actually.
Let me go down in this cave over here again.
Or even here.
Oh yeah.
What did I just hear? I heard a balloon pop.
Like, look at that.
It's actually the same. It doesn't matter which side it's on.
Oh, it is balloons popping.
Fuck it, I'm going down here.
Here's that thing again.
If I hit that with a hammer...
Yeah, look, if I hit that with a hammer...
Oof.
Maybe if I hit it in enough times.
I may try that, actually.
Oh, the yo-yo!
It's insanely good.
Shit. That hurts a lot.
I have a lot of healing. Actually, let me try this.
What did I just do?
I'm not sure what I just did.
I'm going to try once more here.
Actually, I have an idea.
Put down this here.
Oh, no, no, no.
That way we're going to regenerate health.
Wait a minute, let me take care of this guy.
And you know what else?
There we go. Now we're ready for anything.
Is it doing anything to it?
I'm regenerating, sort of, quickly.
It's like a balloon pop.
It's like increasing in speed.
I'm not sure.
What if I remove everything around it?
Wait, I can't remove that.
Let's try a bomb.
Oh, shit.
Let's go this way.
There we go.
Let me try a sticky bomb.
Just get rid of everything below it.
Huh.
There's something going on with that.
Hit it one more time.
Bro.
What is going on with this hammer?
I don't understand.
Oh, shit. That's not what I wanted to do.
Give me this back. Give me this back.
Thank you. Okay, we're moving on.
We are moving on into the cave.
Ooh, it's getting a little...
Ah, here we go. Here we go.
Where can we go?
I want this zoomed in, actually.
Maybe like that.
I can go further down.
No, not... ah, actually.
There's something right below me, no?
No, wait, there's actually not.
But I'm going to dig down anyway.
Oh, shit, I'm...
Ah!
Come on.
Okay, we're fine.
I want to drain this water real bad.
Actually, I can do that.
I'm just going to throw a bunch of bombs.
Oh, shit.
Come on!
Look, it's draining.
I made a hole in the bottom.
Oh, now it's stopped.
Let's see what's down there.
Ooh, here we go.
Oh, um...
Oh, my God, get away from me.
There we go.
Let's bomb some more.
Get away from me.
Oh, no, I didn't mean to...
Shit, I didn't mean to throw bombs everywhere there.
God damn it.
Let's see.
Did we make a hole?
Bro, we are not making any progress here on that.
Wow.
Really?
Actually, we are. Never mind.
Nice.
Wait, I got something.
Screams echo around you.
Oh, no, wait.
Is this...
Is this a sign?
Uh...
I don't know where to go.
Do I go up?
Oh, God.
No!
Lucky break.
Oh, my God. Come on.
There we go.
Uh...
Put down this.
There.
Nice and cozy.
Monster banners.
Sure.
Let's see here.
What do I want to...
Do I have any potions?
Peace's enemy spawn rate.
Actually, I want this.
I think.
And...
Wait, nimble the undertaker.
Quick, 10% speed.
5% speed.
Very...
Very weak knockback.
Okay, I think the one I have is better.
Let it rain right here.
Is there a monster going to appear here?
Come on!
I thought for sure.
Something was going to happen here.
I thought it was like one of those cryptic messages.
Something was about to happen.
Maybe not.
Um...
I really should experiment
whether or not I take damage from those bombs or not.
Wait, I just...
Did you just find a bomb?
Huh?
Oh!
There's items in these.
Recall.
Oh, here we go.
God, it feels good to have a gun!
Feels immaculate.
Actually, do I want this or do I want that?
Fast.
This one has very bad knockback, right?
Let's see here. Let me actually test again.
I feel like this is slower.
Even though it says it's faster.
Am I crazy?
This is kind of a nice weapon.
Man, we are in a cave, huh?
Another one of those things over there.
Get that away from me.
Oh my God, I'm dying!
Okay, you know what? Maybe this one is better.
That was pretty...
No, not that one.
Yeah, that one.
Well, this one.
That's the one I was looking at.
Oh yeah, I have to remember I can do this.
I wonder if that will...
allow me to...
Actually, I do wonder if it protects me from all damage.
Let me in.
Here we go.
Give me that. Oh, fuck, here we go.
Oh, lordy.
Oh, wow.
I feel like the flaming is better here.
Come on, come on. Get back to the fire.
Oh, they're being confused here.
It seems...
See, that works pretty well.
That's what happened last time when I was stuck, remember?
I was in a little bit of a cave there.
Oh, here we go. Look at that big boy.
Look at that big boy.
Oh, shit.
Oh, goodness gracious me.
Fucking just plinking away.
Where's it coming?
I want to try and see if I can sprint through it.
I think that worked okay. I'm not sure.
Back to the campfire.
This is working pretty well.
Look at all the little eyeballs.
They're so nasty.
Cryptane ore.
Yes, dude.
Come on.
Fight me, bitch.
I'm not afraid.
I'm just swinging this here.
Oh, god. Here he comes.
I wonder if there's going to be a phase two when I kill all the small ones.
Speaking of...
I think this may be it.
Plinking away.
Oh, god.
Plink, plink, plink, plink, plink, plink, plink, plink.
I clicked the wrong button, I think.
Use the yo-yo.
What the fuck?
Oh, I'm dead.
Holy shit.
Okay, okay.
Brain's got hands.
Okay.
Well, well, well.
Look at all the crimp-tane ore I got.
Holy shit.
Tissue sample. I need to chest that out.
We need to smell that shit.
This...
Make a shit ton of it.
Dylan?
What is this?
No.
This.
Void vault.
Can be used to store your items.
Stored items can only be accessed by you.
Will contain items picked up by a void bag.
Oh, is it like a remote storage thing?
Summons the void vault.
Functions as an extended inventory when opened
may pick up overflowing items when opened.
Right click to close.
Shit, that sounds
unbelievably amazing.
Wow.
The meatball.
Oh, wait a minute.
The fuck here we go?
Wait, obsidian?
What's yours?
Can I make any of this?
Oh my god.
Holy shit.
I want to make a meatball, I think.
Oh, this?
No, this is a hammer.
55% hammer power.
50% hammer.
Hammer power.
70% pickaxe power, though.
Able to mine hellstone!
I think I have to.
I don't know what hellstone is, but
I think I gotta do it.
I gotta do it?
No?
Bam.
It's way better.
And then...
I'm tempted to make
the meatball!
It seems insane.
Boulder can be placed?
Huh.
Really?
Can I make traps with that?
I'm making it
unpleasant to the meatball.
6% damage and 15%
strong knockback.
Average knockback.
I wonder if it's average knockback
because of the minus 10% knockback.
Or if this version
just IS average knockback.
It's kinda hard to know here.
Let's see here.
Weapons.
I'm gonna store this.
This is better in every single fucking way.
I mean, except the fire, of course.
And we have this one.
It's worse.
Put it in. Wait, what's this? The rotted fork?
Hold on a second.
What is this now?
Oh, it's a spear.
Huh.
Oh, yeah.
Whoa, that has
way larger range.
Oh, yeah, dude.
Oh, that's interesting.
Attack range is...
or attack speed is way better
at a certain range, but if you go too close, look.
Whoa!
Yeah.
Well, then again.
I mean, wow!
That's damage.
But you gotta be close for that.
Holy shit.
No, no, put this one there, of course.
Okay, man.
All kinds of things are happening!
Let's see here.
Let me
put some stuff in here.
I'll take this with me.
This one, I'm not so fan of.
The artery
is cool.
But maybe I'll...
Hmm.
That's a quip.
This has just become weapons.
All of them.
I like the gun.
Oh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
How much money do we have?
Oh, wait, I lost a...
33.
I want to buy that minigun.
But we don't have enough.
Unfortunately.
I think we lost some money down in the
cave just now.
Yeah, put some stuff there.
I want to make special potions
that will make me better.
I want defense potions.
How do I make it?
I need to ask Dylan
about this again.
Dylan, for fuck's sake,
you gotta tell me.
Also, the spiky ball.
Kind of forgot to do that.
This goes in.
Ah, lesser healing potion.
Let's take some of the...
Whatchamacallit.
Oh, actually.
Huh.
Let's do a quick test here.
What first?
Where's the mushroom?
Oh, did I use all the...
Fucking...
Where?
Why is this here?
Sort.
Construction.
Chilanias.
Can this not be stacked?
It cannot.
Let's bring some grenades.
Salmon Abigail.
Misability.
Wait, this is...
Wait, this...
This goes in here.
I can store that there.
Tissue sample.
Actually, put it up here.
I need to quickly figure out if I can make some irons.
Ah, iron skin.
I remember being able to craft that.
But I forgot the ingredients.
You're not going to tell me, are you?
What was it again? Fuck, iron skin.
It was something, wasn't it?
I remember something.
Wait.
Boomerang.
Wow, this requires a mini shark.
Brother.
What's this?
Increased magic.
Damage.
Huh.
That's actually pretty cool. What is sunplate?
It requires sky mill.
The hell?
Fuck.
I don't remember how I'd craft that.
Also, wait, I have a shit ton of bottles.
I'm just going to grab some stuff that I think is needed here.
It was probably one of these, honestly.
Just grab a bunch.
Okay. Let's test the bunch.
Oh, here we go.
Yes.
There it is.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
What do we got?
Garland.
Gender change program.
Provides life gen...
I wonder if some of these will overwrite each other.
Daybloom and mushroom.
This one is Daybloom and iron ore.
Oh.
Do I have that?
I don't think I do, dude.
Or are we talking any iron ore here?
It did say iron ore specifically, didn't it?
Shit.
Nope, actually.
Hey!
Yes!
Ha ha!
There it is.
That's important.
And then...
Let's see here.
What is this again?
Verdebra.
Monster lasagna.
Oh!
Some is the brain of Ketulhu.
Plague bringer's threats.
Unholy arrow.
Petal increases enemy spawn rate.
Yeah, how about no?
How about no, sir?
Grasshopper?
No.
What about this?
Vicious powder spreads the crimson!
I'm gonna be doing that right in front of the dryad.
What about crimson seeds?
Blood?
Wait, 20 damage?
Why would I...
That's what I need.
Did I have that?
Again?
No, but I have all kinds of other...
weird things. Hold on, we need to test that, too.
Oh!
Look at this!
Wait.
Whoops.
Didn't I put...
How do I harvest?
God damn it.
Oh, that's painful.
What the fuck?
Dylan?
What about this shiverthorn?
What can I make?
Prizes and... oh, oh my god.
It's just most swiftly in liquids.
What?
Okay, that requires all kinds of shit.
Love potion.
God damn, dude.
What about acorn?
Oh, you're right.
I mean, this is like the thing, right?
Those falling speed...
Oh, there's two of them!
Because one is with lead, I think.
And the other is with iron.
Makes sense.
Okay.
That's fine for now.
Let's deposit some stuff again.
Sort items.
Sort inventory.
Click this button.
And let's just deposit all kinds of stuff.
And then we have this here.
I'll put that in.
Lens.
It's Michelinius.
The boulder lead ore was in here.
I think we're about ready.
Golden key? Hmm.
Keep it on me, I guess.
I'm intrigued about the boulder.
But here's the thing.
I'm gonna try this.
Wait, how does that work?
How much the eye of...
It doesn't work!
Where is the eye of the tool?
Fine.
I'll put it in ore can.
Ah, Michelinius.
Okay.
Oh, you hear that?
Ah, he's back.
Guys, I gotta go.
I gotta get to take care of him.
Yeah.
That's gotta be it.
Alright, no spoilers in the chat, remember?
Hold on, let me just quickly open.
Here we go.
Okay.
What's up, people?
This was officially the longest stream ever.
Really?
Nice.
I did it.
Wait, even longer than one of the Minecraft ones?
I had a very long Minecraft stream.
Potato, potato, potato, potato, potato, potato.
I agree, Jen.
Thanks for that.
That was a long stream.
You blessed us.
You blessed me.
Terraria.
Why is Terraria so hard to pronounce sometimes?
Has gotcha.
Yep, for sure.
Oliver, you better be streaming this on the weekend
because you got me hooked.
Well, William the 23rd.
I couldn't quite read it before your name went away.
Maybe I will.
Congrats.
I have good tool.
Finally, I got it.
I got it.
Another hour and I'll donate 100.
I'm sorry, man.
I gotta go to bed.
But I appreciate the thought.
Just watch next time.
Soon.
What are you gonna do about the printer, man?
I don't know.
That's between me and him.
Have you seen Terraria April Fools?
I have not.
Did the developers do something funny?
Hi, Oliver.
I'm in Copenhagen now. Long days of the conference,
but it's nice to come back and chill before bed
with these long streams. Thanks.
Hey, nice. I hope you're enjoying your time here.
Actually, today has been pretty good weather.
I hope you were outside enjoying some of it.
Not like me.
Spending all day inside like a...
degenerate.
Just playing video games all day.
Well, that's not true.
I didn't do that all day.
A lot of the day, though.
If we do a sleep stream,
it'll be the new longest stream.
Why would I do that?
Why would anyone watch that?
I know people do it, but I don't get it.
I have 600 hours on this.
It's nice seeing someone new.
Damn.
600 hours.
Holy shit.
Punch her in the face.
I mean...
I guess I could punch the man in the face.
Who's printing.
Hey, Lord Eternal. See you, Oliver. Good night.
May you sleep, tit.
Thank you. May you sleep, tit, as well.
Lord.
You should check out the Minecraft April Fools update.
Everyone is saying you will love it.
Actually, I heard about it.
Something to do with potatoes, isn't it?
Haha.
Hold on, I need to, actually.
Do you guys know how to put Minecraft?
No, not Minecraft.
Fuck, now I have Minecraft on my head.
How to have Terraria music play when you're all tapped?
Because the sound of the game stops when you all tap.
And it's kind of annoying.
Maybe you guys know.
Maybe not.
I don't know.
I haven't been able to find a way.
I was inside all day except for the heavy rain this evening.
I was at the Reffen street food market.
Dude! Nice!
That's a really nice place.
Some really good food there.
Also kind of expensive though.
But yeah, that's really nice.
Don't punch him, he's just printing.
Date the printer man? Nah, man.
You guys know I'm not into that sort of thing.
Now I want to play Terraria too.
You should. John, Joe.
Play it. Do it.
Also, hold on.
I missed some people here.
Oopsie! I don't know if you're here.
Oopsie and Harry sales.
Both joined the potato.
Welcome guys. Sorry, I actually completely
forgot that people were doing this.
Hey, Levy! Good to see you again.
Thanks for the five euros.
Show that I who's the boss.
You're getting close.
Oh nice, that must have been
right before I did it, huh?
I did show that I who was boss.
Spoiler alert.
It was I.
Tupiare Yakikaya.
With
five
Russian
dollars, I think.
Russian rubble
I don't know. I don't know what the currency is,
but thank you. You really thought you were over.
Rain World got a new DLC announced.
You can't escape from the Rain World.
Yeah, I heard about that.
It sounds cool.
And Levy, you gifted
five
memberships to people.
That's freaking awesome. Thank you so much.
I wonder who got them.
I'm curious. Thank you, Levy.
That's really, really generous of you.
I appreciate it.
And then we have Isanti.
The cool profile picture. Thanks for the two euros.
The one-eyed
I is defeated.
Good work.
Nice. Nice reference.
Reference is out of control.
Everyone knows it.
Jen got a membership.
Cool.
That's awesome.
But I guess being a mod overrides that.
So you won't get the green. You still have the blue.
That's cool.
I mean, now you have a wrench and a line.
That's kind of cool that you have both of those.
Hundred rubles, one dollar.
Okay. Okay. Thanks.
Will you play the new Rain World DLC when it comes out?
Um,
maybe.
I think I would have to
have some more to do as well.
Maybe I'll even combine it
with doing the rest of the campaigns that I haven't done yet
in Rain World.
Like it would be a longer thing, but
probably not in the near future.
I feel like I've gotten my ass kicked enough
in that game lately.
I need to, you know...
Man.
You know how it is.
Hahaha.
I can send this now. Yes, you can Milano Chocolate.
Also, is that a discord icon with a
creepy face on it?
I'm curious about that.
It's too powerful.
How you doing?
Mr. Waffles.
That's a great name.
Oliver, you might be able to have the music.
Keep playing with windowed mode.
Nope.
I don't know how you do windowed mode.
The chat goes below the edge of the video
so you can't see the last line, which is quite annoying.
Chat goes...
Yeah, but
I don't know what's wrong with that.
It's um...
Hasn't it always been like this, even in Minecraft
back then? Because I haven't changed
anything.
Are you guys sure there's something wrong
with there?
So hold on.
For me, when I look at
the YouTube chat
and I look at the chat in OBS
it's synchronized completely.
Or is it only in the in-game chat?
If a chat message is more than
one line long, the other line is cut off.
Oh!
Only if...
Okay. Only in-game?
Okay.
Hold on a sec.
Let me actually go back here.
Let me try something real quick.
That's so weird.
I don't know why that is.
I'm gonna copy all the
custom CSS
for the chat of
the waiting screen
and paste it into
the chat
of the in-game one.
Maybe something went wrong there.
No, it's the exact same.
Maybe it's just because
it's so small. There's something wrong with it.
Let's make it like
360.
The chat is a bit bigger now.
Let me ask you something. Was the chat okay last time?
Was it only today?
Can someone write
a long message? Let's just test it
in real time here.
It was same last time.
Oh, it seems fine now.
That seems to work.
Long message!
I mean, it's working now, right?
Okay, you know what I think it is.
I think I made it...
For some reason, if I make the
height of that chat window too
small,
that breaks something.
Which is interesting.
Yeah, but look,
if I move it up, it's just this.
It's not like the rest
is below like this, you know?
Do I exist?
Do you?
I don't know.
Probably because it wants to load in every...
Yeah, maybe. I have no clue.
But I'm glad that it works now.
Also, it's a bit bigger now, which is nice, I guess.
But
if there's no room for every message,
it delays.
Okay.
Okay, well, great!
It works now. I'm happy about that.
Terraria is a video game.
That is... that's true.
That is indeed true.
You're the awesome chat transition
which I say.
Okay, hold on.
That's so fucking cool.
And it didn't take that long to set up either.
It's like a simple OBS thing.
And I didn't even know I could do it
until I figured it out.
Now I know how all the big streamers
do these awesome transitions
and stuff.
It's not really useful for anything.
I just did it because it's
cool to have, I guess.
Okay, yeah. I'm going to try again.
Oliver, have you really not heard of Cthulhu of Lovecraft?
Bloodborne was heavily influenced.
No, I mean, I've heard
of Cthulhu.
I've seen the name many times
but I never really knew what it was.
Also, I know
I also haven't read any Lovecraft
stuff before, so
yeah.
It's all very
obscured to me still.
I see hints of green on the tree and grass.
What are you talking about, Bailey?
Are you okay?
That was my chance to say hi to Oliver.
What's up, Sir Frank? How you doing?
I mean, that's fine. Lovecraft
was slightly xenophobic anyway.
Literally, okay.
I mean,
if it's like otherworldly monsters
coming in to ruin everyone's day,
I think it's okay to hate on those monsters.
If that's what you're talking about.
Shout out to Sir Frank, indeed.
Sir Frank
The Knight.
What even is Lovecraft?
Is it a book or what? That's what they are.
Exactly. Aimbot, XD.
I actually don't know either.
I think it's a genre
or is it a book?
Will Noida be after Terraria asking
as a big fan of both?
News of PE.
What is PE?
Anyway,
maybe Noida. We'll see.
It really depends how I feel after
the game is done.
I can't really say. It really just depends
on what I feel like playing.
Would you ever play Stardew Valley?
I actually did play it
recently
with a friend of mine
for a little bit.
I didn't get very far though.
I think we spent maybe three hours
in the game in total.
Maybe four hours.
Maybe I'll play it
more one day.
Ten more minutes. You can do this all
there.
What happens in ten minutes?
Oh.
I don't know if I'm ready to do that.
That's seven hours.
Oh man, that's a long time.
How does it feel to have all this sudden growth?
It's so weird.
I don't understand it.
It just happened out of nowhere.
One day I put up
Out of Wiles and then people are like
What's up? I love Out of Wiles.
Play, play.
Play.
And the funny thing is I didn't advertise that
anywhere.
I think I just got lucky with the YouTube
algorithm just suggesting it to people.
I kind of wish I could focus a bit more
on it because it's really fun
to do this whole YouTube thing.
But I also have my work to think on.
And all kinds of other
real life stuff happening.
Feels like the subs are being printed.
I found the Out of Wiles because
of this supercut guy.
Yeah, that was super cool.
He did message me to ask
if he could make a supercut of it in case
you guys were wondering.
Catullu was a creature Lovecraft
wrote about too. Oh, Lovecraft was a
guy.
Huh.
Came from Hollow Knight
obesity. Nothing more fun than
a spoiler-free adventure in a game with
too many secrets.
Yeah.
I know how you feel.
I've been watching some Out of Wiles
list plays as well after
I finished that game.
It's a lot of fun.
I've been watching
Apocalypse and
Little Indigestion.
It was awesome.
For anyone looking for
another Out of Wiles series, Joseph
Anderson played it.
Isn't he the guy who also makes
like very long reviews
of games?
I haven't actually seen any of them, but
I feel like I've had that recommended on my
YouTube page for a while.
In my case, at least,
I specifically searched for blind
Out of Wiles playthrough to replay it by proxy.
Yeah,
I feel that. I went through the same
thing after I finished
The Last of Us.
The Last of Us 1 and 2.
I just couldn't get enough watching other people play that game.
Fucking love that
game. And I love watching
other people play it.
So much fun
and really sad as well.
Anderson also streams and has
a habit of breaking
every game he touches.
What do you mean breaking them?
What do you mean like doing things
like glitching through walls and stuff?
Or something?
Descending, replaying by proxy
is really something else.
I watch so much stuff blind to
re-experience games.
I mean, it's a cool experience to see
how other people
deal with it, right?
It's like watching a movie
and then talking about it with friends.
Or even better, showing a movie
that you really like to someone.
It's just entertaining to share
that fun you have with someone
else.
He's the perfect play tester bug finder
as Jacques.
I bet he's the guy who walks into
a bar and asks where the toilet
is.
Right?
I don't know if any of you are going to get that one.
I'm basically replaying Terraria by proxy
right now. No, you're not.
Because right now, nothing is happening.
You liar.
I really like the community you've built
here. This is a nice environment.
Here's the thing, I didn't do much.
I made the discord server and set some things up
and people... it's the people that did it.
I mean, the community is
freaking awesome.
And I did very little.
People did the rest.
They decided to get the whole
Minecraft server going and
they are making
um...
what is it called? Bingo cards
for things. It's just super cool.
I didn't play a hand in
that at all.
It's such a cool community.
A man walks into a bar.
He asks where the bathroom is.
The bar goes up and plays.
It's exactly...
Exactly fell on 00.
That's exactly it.
That's such a good one.
Cool people attract cool people.
True.
Okay.
It's time for me to bounce on
out of here, people.
I gotta get some small stuff
done and then it's time
for me to go to sleep.
I was up sort of early today, so
that's why I started the stream
a little bit earlier today than usual
just so I can
get that playtime in.
I can stop it any time I want.
I swear.
Stop him!
No!
It's time.
Alright people
we're gonna have to break that
7-hour mark some other time.
But for tonight
I bid you adios.